<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carnage on Crash Count</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/</link><description>Recent content in Carnage on Crash Count</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Another Life Lost at Northern &amp; Parsons. How Many More?</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-23--2025-03-09-2025-03-15/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-23--2025-03-09-2025-03-15/</guid><description>She stepped into the crosswalk. The minivan came fast. It never stopped. She was 78. She will never be 79. Northern Boulevard claims another life. The city knew this would happen. It will happen again. How many more must die?</description></item><item><title>He Crossed. He Died. The City Shrugged.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-16--2025-03-02-2025-03-08/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-16--2025-03-02-2025-03-08/</guid><description>Chaosheng Wu, 80, was struck and killed while crossing Hylan Boulevard in Staten Island. The driver stayed. No charges were filed. The city moved on. With 1,555 crashes in a single week, how many more lives will be lost before action is taken?</description></item><item><title>She Had Dreams. He Had No License. Now She’s Gone—And NYC Let It Happen.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-09--2025-02-23-2025-03-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-09--2025-02-23-2025-03-01/</guid><description>She worked three jobs. She dreamed of becoming a nurse. Then an unlicensed driver ran a stop sign, crashed, and fled—leaving Imani Vance dying in the front seat. He shouldn’t have been on the road. New York let it happen. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>Another Cyclist Dead. Another Family Shattered. NYC Knew—And Did Nothing.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-02--2025-02-16-2025-02-22/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-02--2025-02-16-2025-02-22/</guid><description>Two cyclists hit. One died instantly. One never woke up. Hours later, another body hit the pavement. Blood pooled. Bones shattered. The city knew this would happen. It knows how to stop it. But it won’t. And it will happen again.</description></item><item><title>A Senior Died Steps from Safety. NYC Let It Happen.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-23--2025-02-09-2025-02-15/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-23--2025-02-09-2025-02-15/</guid><description>She lived in a home meant for care. The minivan tore through that illusion. One crash. One death. Three injured. Another senior lost in a city that moves too slow. New York knew this would happen. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>90 Years in NYC—Killed in Seconds. No Charges. No Change.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-16--2025-02-02-2025-02-08/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-16--2025-02-02-2025-02-08/</guid><description>Frances Rickard survived 90 years in New York. One U-turn ended it. A taxi struck her. Another car finished the job. No charges. No change. The city lets its elders die in the crosswalk. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>She Survived the Nazis and Chernobyl—But Not New York’s Streets.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-09--2025-01-26-2025-02-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-09--2025-01-26-2025-02-01/</guid><description>She outran the Nazis. She endured Chernobyl. She outlived a pandemic. At 95, Mayya Gil was still standing—until a New York street took her life. The driver walked away. She did not. How many more will the city let fall?</description></item><item><title>He Worked While NYC Slept. The City Never Protected Him.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-02--2025-01-19-2025-01-25/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-02--2025-01-19-2025-01-25/</guid><description>Mamadou Barry worked nights so his kids could see him in the daylight. One shift ended with his SUV in ruins, his body buried in wreckage. The city knew night workers faced danger. It let him die anyway. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>She Walked. He Drove. She Died. NYC Let It Happen.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-26--2025-01-12-2025-01-18/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-26--2025-01-12-2025-01-18/</guid><description>She crossed at the light. The sedan turned anyway. Metal met flesh. Bone met pavement. She was 70. She will never be 71. The city knew this would happen. It did nothing. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>The Light Was Red. She Had the Right of Way. She Died Anyway.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-19--2025-01-05-2025-01-11/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-19--2025-01-05-2025-01-11/</guid><description>The girl was small. The SUV was not. She crossed with the light. The driver turned anyway. She died on the asphalt. The city knew this would happen. It will happen again. Another child. Another street. Another promise too late.</description></item><item><title>Hit, Dragged, Forgotten: NYC’s Streets Keep Killing the Vulnerable</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-12--2024-12-29-2025-01-04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-12--2024-12-29-2025-01-04/</guid><description>Michael Foster begged for change at a Brooklyn stoplight. A speeding Audi struck him, dragged him for blocks, and disappeared into the night. No arrests. No justice. Just another name lost on the city’s deadliest streets. How many more?</description></item></channel></rss>