<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carnage on Crash Count</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/</link><description>Recent content in Carnage on Crash Count</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NYC’s Deadly Streets: 38 Lives Lost, and Still No Action</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-03-10-2025-02-24_to_2025-03-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-03-10-2025-02-24_to_2025-03-02/</guid><description>Seven more lives lost. A 26-year-old in a wrecked Mercedes. A 23-year-old hit by a speeding, drunk firefighter. A baby in a crosswalk. The city has the power to stop this. It refuses. Demand action before next week’s toll rises again.</description></item><item><title>One More Dead, Hundreds More Hurt: NYC’s Streets Keep Taking Lives</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-03-03-2025-02-17_to_2025-02-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-03-03-2025-02-17_to_2025-02-23/</guid><description>A cyclist dead. A toddler injured. Over 800 hurt in one week. New York City&amp;rsquo;s streets keep taking lives. Thirty-one dead this year, thousands more suffering. Change is possible, but leaders hesitate. How many more must fall before action is taken?</description></item><item><title>Six Dead This Week. Thirty This Year. How Many More?</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-02-24-2025-02-10_to_2025-02-16/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-02-24-2025-02-10_to_2025-02-16/</guid><description>Six more dead. Hundreds injured. The city&amp;rsquo;s streets remain violent. Speed kills, and New York has the power to slow it down—but refuses. Change won’t come unless we demand it.</description></item><item><title>Six More Dead. Another Week of Blood on NYC Streets.</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-02-17-2025-02-03_to_2025-02-09/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-02-17-2025-02-03_to_2025-02-09/</guid><description>Six dead in one week. A 90-year-old crushed by two cars. A Tesla driver incinerated in a crash. The year’s toll: 24 dead. The solution is simple—lower the speed. The city can do it now, but will they? Demand action before more lives are lost.</description></item><item><title>Another Week, Another Four Dead: NYC’s Streets Keep Killing</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-02-10-2025-01-27_to_2025-02-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-02-10-2025-01-27_to_2025-02-02/</guid><description>Four more dead. Nearly 750 injured. NYC’s streets remain a battlefield. Speed kills, and the city refuses to act. Lower the limit to 20 mph now—before more lives are lost.</description></item><item><title>Seven More Dead: Another Week in NYC’s Traffic War</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-02-03-2025-01-20_to_2025-01-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-02-03-2025-01-20_to_2025-01-26/</guid><description>Seven more dead. A Holocaust survivor struck in Brooklyn. A father lost in Queens. The toll keeps rising. The city has the power to slow cars and save lives. It hasn&amp;rsquo;t acted. Demand action now before next week&amp;rsquo;s numbers bring more heartbreak.</description></item><item><title>Four More Dead. The Blood on NYC’s Streets Won’t Stop.</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-01-27-2025-01-13_to_2025-01-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-01-27-2025-01-13_to_2025-01-19/</guid><description>Another week, another four dead. Over 1,600 crashes. Nearly 1,000 injured. Speed cameras help, but the city still won’t lower speed limits. The bloodshed continues while leaders wait. Demand change before the next death.</description></item><item><title>Two More Dead. How Many More Before We Act?</title><link>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-01-20-2025-01-06_to_2025-01-12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcount.github.io/carnage/2025-01-20-2025-01-06_to_2025-01-12/</guid><description>Two dead. Over a thousand injured. This was just the first weeks of 2025. Vision Zero promised safety, but traffic violence continues. City leaders have the power to lower speed limits. They haven’t. How many more must die before they act?</description></item></channel></rss>