<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crash Count</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/</link><description>Recent content on Crash Count</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://crashcountnyc.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Steel Rolls On. We Bury the Names.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-04-14--2025-03-30-2025-04-05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-04-14--2025-03-30-2025-04-05/</guid><description>A man dies alone on 9th Avenue before dawn. A child’s knee crushed in Brooklyn. Two kids run down in Queens. Three dead, 722 hurt in one week. The city keeps driving. Names vanish. Only the street remembers.</description></item><item><title>Background for Shahana Hanif</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/background/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/background/</guid><description>Council Member Shahana Hanif has been one of the Council&amp;rsquo;s most outspoken advocates for safer streets. She consistently fights to redesign dangerous roads and slow down cars. Hanif believes no pedestrian or cyclist should fear for their life on city streets. When crashes happen, she shows up, demands action, and follows through. From pushing for protected bike lanes to championing lower speed limits, her record is clear. She stands firmly on the side of vulnerable road users, working to put people above cars at every turn.</description></item><item><title>Kalman Yeger resisted street safety reforms</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/background/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/background/</guid><description>Councilmember Kalman Yeger consistently opposed most citywide efforts to protect pedestrians and cyclists. He voted against speed cameras, daylighting, and Vision Zero street redesigns. While occasionally backing hyper-local fixes, his record favored drivers and framed safety reforms as overreach.</description></item><item><title>Three Kids. One Mom. One Street. All Gone.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-04-02--2025-03-23-2025-03-29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-04-02--2025-03-23-2025-03-29/</guid><description>Ocean Parkway. One green light. One stroller. Three children. One mother. An Audi flew through them like they weren’t real. Now Philip is four, motherless, kidney gone. He lives. His sisters do not. The street didn’t stop. Neither did the city.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4801962 on 2025-03-29</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4801962/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4801962/</guid><description>Ocean Parkway near Quentin Road, Brooklyn — A sedan driven by an unlicensed woman ran the light. A mother and her three children were in the crosswalk. The signal was theirs. Three died. One, age four, lay crushed and still.</description></item><item><title>The Cars Are Killing Us. The City’s Still Blaming Bikes.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-29--2025-03-16-2025-03-21/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-29--2025-03-16-2025-03-21/</guid><description>A toddler’s leg crushed. An elder left bleeding. A man broken in a crosswalk. All struck by cars. No headlines. No fury. Just silence. The city blamed a bike—and looked away from the steel that does the killing.</description></item><item><title>Another Life Lost at Northern &amp; Parsons. How Many More?</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-23--2025-03-09-2025-03-15/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-23--2025-03-09-2025-03-15/</guid><description>She stepped into the crosswalk. The minivan came fast. It never stopped. She was 78. She will never be 79. Northern Boulevard claims another life. The city knew this would happen. It will happen again. How many more must die?</description></item><item><title>He Crossed. He Died. The City Shrugged.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-16--2025-03-02-2025-03-08/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-16--2025-03-02-2025-03-08/</guid><description>Chaosheng Wu, 80, was struck and killed while crossing Hylan Boulevard in Staten Island. The driver stayed. No charges were filed. The city moved on. With 1,555 crashes in a single week, how many more lives will be lost before action is taken?</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4797969 on 2025-03-11</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4797969/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4797969/</guid><description>Coney Island Ave near Avenue K — A southbound box truck struck a 44-year-old man crossing without a signal. He fell hard. Blood on the pavement. Head wounds. Deep cuts. The truck’s right bumper bore the mark. He did not wake.</description></item><item><title>She Had Dreams. He Had No License. Now She’s Gone—And NYC Let It Happen.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-09--2025-02-23-2025-03-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-09--2025-02-23-2025-03-01/</guid><description>She worked three jobs. She dreamed of becoming a nurse. Then an unlicensed driver ran a stop sign, crashed, and fled—leaving Imani Vance dying in the front seat. He shouldn’t have been on the road. New York let it happen. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>Another Cyclist Dead. Another Family Shattered. NYC Knew—And Did Nothing.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-02--2025-02-16-2025-02-22/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-03-02--2025-02-16-2025-02-22/</guid><description>Two cyclists hit. One died instantly. One never woke up. Hours later, another body hit the pavement. Blood pooled. Bones shattered. The city knew this would happen. It knows how to stop it. But it won’t. And it will happen again.</description></item><item><title>Take Action: Slow the Speed, Stop the Carnage</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/take_action/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/take_action/</guid><description>Demand immediate action to reduce traffic violence in NYC by lowering the citywide speed limit to 20 mph and protecting life-saving speed cameras.</description></item><item><title>A Senior Died Steps from Safety. NYC Let It Happen.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-23--2025-02-09-2025-02-15/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-23--2025-02-09-2025-02-15/</guid><description>She lived in a home meant for care. The minivan tore through that illusion. One crash. One death. Three injured. Another senior lost in a city that moves too slow. New York knew this would happen. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>90 Years in NYC—Killed in Seconds. No Charges. No Change.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-16--2025-02-02-2025-02-08/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-16--2025-02-02-2025-02-08/</guid><description>Frances Rickard survived 90 years in New York. One U-turn ended it. A taxi struck her. Another car finished the job. No charges. No change. The city lets its elders die in the crosswalk. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>She Survived the Nazis and Chernobyl—But Not New York’s Streets.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-09--2025-01-26-2025-02-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-09--2025-01-26-2025-02-01/</guid><description>She outran the Nazis. She endured Chernobyl. She outlived a pandemic. At 95, Mayya Gil was still standing—until a New York street took her life. The driver walked away. She did not. How many more will the city let fall?</description></item><item><title>About the Count of Crashes</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/about/</guid><description>The slow-motion catastrophe of traffic violence in New York City.</description></item><item><title>He Worked While NYC Slept. The City Never Protected Him.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-02--2025-01-19-2025-01-25/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-02-02--2025-01-19-2025-01-25/</guid><description>Mamadou Barry worked nights so his kids could see him in the daylight. One shift ended with his SUV in ruins, his body buried in wreckage. The city knew night workers faced danger. It let him die anyway. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>New York's Streets are a war zone</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/rants/2025-01-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/rants/2025-01-27/</guid><description>If a plane crashed in Times Square every month, we’d shut the skies down. But traffic violence quietly claims lives every week. The Count of Crashes documents the human cost—no spin, no excuses, just the blunt truth.</description></item><item><title>She Walked. He Drove. She Died. NYC Let It Happen.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-26--2025-01-12-2025-01-18/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-26--2025-01-12-2025-01-18/</guid><description>She crossed at the light. The sedan turned anyway. Metal met flesh. Bone met pavement. She was 70. She will never be 71. The city knew this would happen. It did nothing. It will happen again.</description></item><item><title>The Light Was Red. She Had the Right of Way. She Died Anyway.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-19--2025-01-05-2025-01-11/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-19--2025-01-05-2025-01-11/</guid><description>The girl was small. The SUV was not. She crossed with the light. The driver turned anyway. She died on the asphalt. The city knew this would happen. It will happen again. Another child. Another street. Another promise too late.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4785728 on 2025-01-13</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4785728/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4785728/</guid><description>Brooklyn-Queens Expressway — A 73-year-old man lost consciousness at the wheel. His Ford SUV veered left, crushing into a Lexus. Belted, chest shattered, he died in his seat. Illness struck first. Steel and speed did the rest.</description></item><item><title>Hit, Dragged, Forgotten: NYC’s Streets Keep Killing the Vulnerable</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-12--2024-12-29-2025-01-04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/carnage/2025-01-12--2024-12-29-2025-01-04/</guid><description>Michael Foster begged for change at a Brooklyn stoplight. A speeding Audi struck him, dragged him for blocks, and disappeared into the night. No arrests. No justice. Just another name lost on the city’s deadliest streets. How many more?</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4777578 on 2024-12-09</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4777578/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4777578/</guid><description>McDonald Ave near 1695 — A 2012 sedan turned left. The front end folded. A 27-year-old woman, unbelted in the passenger seat, struck her head. She stayed awake. Crush wounds spread. The air stank of alcohol.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4775450 on 2024-12-01</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4775450/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4775450/</guid><description>Corner of East 12th Street and Avenue L — A Jeep turned right. A 73-year-old woman crossed with the light. The front struck her head. No damage to the car. She died in the crosswalk, crushed where she stood.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4774039 on 2024-11-24</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4774039/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4774039/</guid><description>McDonald Ave near Bay Parkway, Brooklyn — A van veered, struck a station wagon. The SUV’s driver, 54, died belted in place. The airbag burst. His body broke inside. Two others rode in the van. The lane change was not safe.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4771373 on 2024-11-13</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4771373/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4771373/</guid><description>Ocean Parkway and Avenue P — Two sedans struck head-on. Steel folded. A man gripped his chest, breath shallow. A woman bled from the head, eyes open. Both belted. Both broken. The light faded, and the engines went still.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4770876 on 2024-11-12</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4770876/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4770876/</guid><description>Near 5th Avenue and 39th Street, a motorcycle clipped a sedan pulling into a spot. Metal shrieked. A woman, 52, helmeted, crushed her leg. Northbound traffic. One slowed. One didn’t. The pavement held the silence.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4769882 on 2024-11-07</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4769882/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4769882/</guid><description>59th Street and 12th Avenue, Brooklyn — A Ford SUV struck a one-year-old boy. No crosswalk. No cry. He lay still on the pavement, head bloodied, body crushed. The bumper bore the mark. The street held its breath.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4764626 on 2024-10-17</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4764626/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4764626/</guid><description>Union Street near 9th Avenue — A woman pedaled west. The sign was missed. She flew, struck head-first. Her helmet held. Blood pooled. She stayed awake. The bike was whole. Her body was not. The street stayed silent.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4759843 on 2024-09-28</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4759843/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4759843/</guid><description>Corner of Avenue L and Coney Island Avenue — A 50-year-old woman, crossing with the light, struck in the head by a turning SUV. She bled onto the pavement. The driver was licensed. The vehicle showed no damage.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4752262 on 2024-09-01</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4752262/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4752262/</guid><description>Avenue O near East 4th Street — A KIA turned left. An e-bike passed right. Metal met speed. A 21-year-old man flew, helmetless. His body hit pavement. Skin split. He stayed awake. He bled.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4749410 on 2024-08-19</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4749410/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4749410/</guid><description>Ditmas Avenue near Coney Island Avenue — A box truck turned right. A 16-year-old on a Hurley e-bike was crushed beneath its front. No helmet. No license. His chest gave way. He was thrown. He died there. The truck rolled on, untouched.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4735930 on 2024-06-26</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4735930/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4735930/</guid><description>Corner of Bond and Butler, Brooklyn — An 83-year-old woman, crossing without a signal, was struck by a turning dump truck. The truck showed no damage. Her body bore the weight of steel, silence, and final breath.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4733755 on 2024-06-17</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4733755/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4733755/</guid><description>Corner of 54th Street and 15th Avenue — A 67-year-old man crossed against the light. A southbound Dodge pickup struck him head-on. He died beneath its front end, his head broken, the truck’s lights shining down on stillness.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4727274 on 2024-05-23</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4727274/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4727274/</guid><description>Corner of 8th Avenue and Union Street — Two sedans collided head-on. Metal folded. A 46-year-old man, unbelted, crushed at the knee. Both drivers distracted. The street fell quiet, holding the weight of what could not be undone.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4720231 on 2024-04-23</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4720231/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4720231/</guid><description>Park Circle and Coney Island Avenue — A 17-year-old boy on a bike, no helmet, struck by an SUV. Thrown hard. Cut deep. His whole body broken. Shock glazed his eyes. Steel front met soft flesh. The pavement held him.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4717690 on 2024-04-16</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4717690/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4717690/</guid><description>Ocean Parkway and Avenue S — A 16-year-old boy on a bike struck a turning sedan. He flew forward, helmet cracked, face torn. He lay still on the asphalt, blood pooling, as morning drivers passed without slowing.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4713401 on 2024-03-29</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4713401/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4713401/</guid><description>Corner of 14th Avenue and 39th Street — A 74-year-old woman stepped into the crosswalk against the light. A northbound Honda SUV struck her head-on. She died there, crushed and broken, her head bleeding on the Brooklyn pavement.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4711853 on 2024-03-23</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4711853/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4711853/</guid><description>18th Avenue near 55th Street, Brooklyn — A moped slammed into the rear of a stopped SUV. The 22-year-old rider flew off, head first. No helmet. No chance. He died alone in the street before the sun rose.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4699806 on 2024-02-03</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4699806/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4699806/</guid><description>Carroll Street near Bond — A Genesis SUV turned left. A moped turned right. The rider, unlicensed and bare, was thrown and crushed. Blood pooled. A leg shattered. The light was ignored. The street did not forgive.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4699808 on 2024-02-03</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4699808/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4699808/</guid><description>Union Street and 6th Avenue — An 83-year-old man crossing with the light. A taxi turns. Steel meets flesh. He falls. Blood pools on the pavement. Head split. Eyes open. The cab did not stop. The street did not forgive.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4695874 on 2024-01-17</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4695874/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4695874/</guid><description>Avenue P — Two sedans collided at speed. The KIA struck left and low. A baby boy, not in the road, not in a car, bled from the head. He was conscious. The metal was twisted. The silence came after.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4692482 on 2024-01-03</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4692482/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4692482/</guid><description>Corner of 17th Avenue and 52nd Street — A Chevy SUV hit an 18-year-old woman crossing with the light. Blood streamed down her face. She stayed awake. The driver looked too late. The streetlights blinked. Traffic rolled on.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4692501 on 2024-01-03</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4692501/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4692501/</guid><description>Corner of 60th Street and 18th Avenue. A woman crossed with the light. An e-scooter came fast, struck her face. Blood spilled on the crosswalk. She stayed awake. The scooter crumpled. So did something else.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4691871 on 2024-01-01</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4691871/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4691871/</guid><description>Brooklyn Queens Expressway — A Jeep lost a tire and slammed forward. Metal folded. Seven inside. In the right rear, a man screamed. His leg crushed. He wore a harness. He did not move. The road stayed quiet.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4690798 on 2023-12-28</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4690798/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4690798/</guid><description>Flatbush Avenue at 5th Avenue — A taxi struck a 72-year-old woman crossing against the light. The front end crushed her. She died there, in the dark, alone on the asphalt. By sunrise, the street was still.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4685716 on 2023-12-07</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4685716/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4685716/</guid><description>Avenue F near McDonald Avenue, Brooklyn — A 12-year-old boy, crossing with the light, took an SUV’s front to the face. Blood pooled on cold asphalt. The driver stayed seated. The vehicle bore no mark. The boy stayed conscious.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4687736 on 2023-12-06</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4687736/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4687736/</guid><description>Ocean Avenue near Parkside — A 90-year-old woman, crossing with the light, struck head-on by a turning sedan. She fell hard. Blood on her face. The car kept moving. She stayed there, conscious, with deep cuts and a wounded head.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4672391 on 2023-10-20</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4672391/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4672391/</guid><description>Sterling Place near 5th Avenue — A 31-year-old man flew from his bike. His arm split open. Blood pooled on the street. An SUV idled, untouched. A passenger turned their head. The crash came from silence, not steel.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4666944 on 2023-10-01</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4666944/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4666944/</guid><description>Flatbush Avenue near 450: An electric sedan slammed a parked Jeep. The unbelted driver flew through the dark. A woman in back, helmeted, was torn at the leg. Both lay bleeding on the street, awake, broken, and still.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4655140 on 2023-08-18</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4655140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4655140/</guid><description>Corner of Atlantic Avenue and Court Street — Two sedans collided before dawn. Steel screamed. An 18-year-old woman, belted in the front seat, died on impact. Her body stayed still while the city stirred and sirens wailed too late.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4649253 on 2023-07-24</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4649253/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4649253/</guid><description>East 10th Street and Avenue O — A 71-year-old man crossed against the light. A Lexus reversed. Metal met bone. He lay semiconscious beneath the rear bumper. He died there, in the dark, under the car that backed into him.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4648149 on 2023-07-23</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4648149/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4648149/</guid><description>McDonald Avenue near Webster: A 68-year-old woman crossing the street was struck head-on by a southbound Lexus SUV. Her body broke beneath the front end. The driver was distracted. She died there. The street fell silent.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4642190 on 2023-07-02</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4642190/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4642190/</guid><description>Bay Parkway near McDonald Avenue — A man turned left on a TAIZH moped, distracted. He flew from the seat. Blood soaked his arm. Helmet on. Permit only. The front crumpled. He lay in shock, bleeding into the summer heat.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4643200 on 2023-06-30</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4643200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4643200/</guid><description>Caton Avenue near Dahill Road — A 35-year-old man, unlicensed and helmetless, slammed his motorcycle into the side of an SUV. He flew from the bike, struck head-first, and died on the street. The SUV driver was unharmed.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4641638 on 2023-06-27</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4641638/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4641638/</guid><description>Avenue M — A 77-year-old woman, crossing with the signal, was struck in the head by a turning Chevy sedan. She bled in the crosswalk. The car, undamaged. The driver, licensed. The light, green. The street, silent.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4634151 on 2023-05-31</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4634151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4634151/</guid><description>Flatbush Avenue near 450: A sedan turned across the lane. A scooter struck hard. The rider flew, hit asphalt. Blood spilled from his leg. No helmet. No gear. Just a man, broken, conscious, bleeding into the morning light.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4624826 on 2023-04-29</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4624826/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4624826/</guid><description>Near 4th Avenue and 6th Street, an e-bike struck a woman in the head. She was not in the road. Blood ran from deep cuts. She stayed conscious. The bike rode on, its front unmarred.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4618563 on 2023-04-05</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4618563/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4618563/</guid><description>Corner of 13th Avenue and 50th Street — A young man crossed. Two SUVs collided. One struck him. His body shattered under the weight. He died there, in the street, as headlights burned through the dusk.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4607398 on 2023-02-17</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4607398/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4607398/</guid><description>Intersection near 621 Hicks Street, Brooklyn — A southbound Lexus struck a 36-year-old man walking with traffic. The sedan’s front crumpled. The man lay bleeding from the head, silent on the asphalt, under the streetlight’s cold glow.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4606313 on 2023-02-12</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4606313/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4606313/</guid><description>Coney Island Avenue near Avenue C — A Toyota’s brakes failed. It plowed into two stopped sedans. Metal crumpled. A 51-year-old man sat belted, his face crushed. Six others waited in silence, the night split by sirens and bent steel.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4598382 on 2023-01-11</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4598382/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4598382/</guid><description>Corner of 17th Avenue and 59th Street — Two SUVs collided mid-afternoon. One ignored the light. Metal crumpled. A 28-year-old man drove. A 29-year-old sat beside him. Both conscious. Both bleeding. Lap belts held them while glass carved their skin.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4581818 on 2022-11-12</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4581818/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4581818/</guid><description>Union Street near 6th Avenue — A Honda SUV plowed into a stopped Kia. In the front seat, a 70-year-old woman cried out. Her back broken. Something gone. She was conscious. Both drivers had looked away.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4580866 on 2022-11-09</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4580866/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4580866/</guid><description>Hicks Street near 509 — A man, 38, slumped dead behind the wheel of a parked 2022 Lexus. Head wound. No seatbelt. Only a child restraint. The car silent. The street colder.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4580944 on 2022-11-09</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4580944/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4580944/</guid><description>Saint Marks Place near 3rd Avenue — A speeding sedan plowed through parked cars. Metal crumpled. A 22-year-old man, unbelted, crushed his arm. Eight records, same name, same wound. The street held the echo of torn steel and pain.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4579733 on 2022-11-07</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4579733/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4579733/</guid><description>Fort Hamilton Parkway near 54th Street — A 23-year-old man on an e-bike, no helmet, struck by a sedan. Ejected. Head split. Blood on the asphalt. Unconscious. Dead before sunrise. Traffic control ignored.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4572961 on 2022-10-14</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4572961/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4572961/</guid><description>Avenue L near East 17th Street — A 49-year-old man on an e-scooter was struck head-on by a westbound Mercedes. The scooter was crushed. He wore no helmet. Speed and inexperience ended him. His body was thrown. He died there.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4572613 on 2022-10-12</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4572613/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4572613/</guid><description>Parkside Avenue, near the Flatbush trees — a 25-year-old cyclist struck by a diesel truck while passing. She was thrown, crushed, and killed. Her bike lay twisted. The truck rolled on, untouched. The morning air held no sound.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4567647 on 2022-09-18</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4567647/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4567647/</guid><description>3rd Avenue near 383rd Street, Brooklyn. A sedan slammed into the back of a parked diesel truck. The driver, 35, cried out—his back broken, pain sharp. He wasn’t thrown. He didn’t move. The report called it “Apparent Death.”</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4561277 on 2022-09-06</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4561277/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4561277/</guid><description>Avenue P near 273rd—just past midnight. A taxi and a sedan met head-on in the dark. A woman in the back, belted and crushed. Her neck throbbed. The taxi driver had no license. Alcohol hung in the air.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4561432 on 2022-09-05</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4561432/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4561432/</guid><description>Prospect Park Southwest at Greenwood Avenue — Two bikes collided head-on. A 23-year-old rider hit the ground hard. No helmet. Blood ran from his leg. Skin peeled back. He stayed awake, staring at the sky while the street held its breath.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4556993 on 2022-08-02</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4556993/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4556993/</guid><description>Near 1654 60th Street, Brooklyn — A Honda SUV backed into the night. The e-bike hit hard. A 33-year-old man clutched his bleeding arm. Flesh torn. Blood on the pavement. The SUV’s rear dented. The street held its breath.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4550242 on 2022-07-26</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4550242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4550242/</guid><description>Bay Parkway, near Council District 44 — A 21-year-old e-bike rider, unlicensed and unhelmeted, was struck head-on by an unlicensed SUV. Thrown from the bike, he lay unconscious, bleeding from the head. Traffic control disregarded. No helmet. No chance.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4543764 on 2022-07-01</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4543764/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4543764/</guid><description>Caton Avenue near East 4th Street, Brooklyn — A 61-year-old man on an e-bike struck the side of a parked Kia. Metal folded. The bike stopped. He did not rise. The street held its breath.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4537823 on 2022-06-15</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4537823/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4537823/</guid><description>Corner of 5th Street and 4th Avenue, Brooklyn — A sedan turned left. A cyclist rode straight. Steel met skin. He flew, face-first to asphalt. Blood pooled. He was 58. He was conscious.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4532525 on 2022-05-30</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4532525/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4532525/</guid><description>Avenue P and West 1st Street, Brooklyn — A 65-year-old man crossed with the light. A taxi struck him head-on. His pelvis shattered. He died where he fell. The SUV and parked cars bore the crash. The signal was ignored.</description></item><item><title>Council District 39 — Crash 4524747 on 2022-05-04</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4524747/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/39/timeline/4524747/</guid><description>Union Street near Clinton, Brooklyn — A taxi struck an eastbound e-scooter. The rider, 40, flew off. No helmet. Blood streamed from his arm. The brakes had failed. He lay conscious on the pavement, staring up at the sky.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4522798 on 2022-04-15</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4522798/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4522798/</guid><description>Corner of 13th Avenue and 51st Street — A Volvo turned right. A woman crossed against the light. The SUV did not stop. Her arm was torn off. She died there, though her body still moved.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4501631 on 2022-02-09</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4501631/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4501631/</guid><description>East 12th Street—A 2012 BMW turned right. Its front bumper struck a five-year-old boy standing off the road. His small body broke beneath the metal. He never woke. The driver stayed licensed. The boy stayed dead.</description></item><item><title>Council District 44 — Crash 4497835 on 2022-01-27</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4497835/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/council-district/44/timeline/4497835/</guid><description>Coney Island Avenue near 1358 — A 13-year-old girl crossed against the light. A southbound box truck struck her. She fell, bleeding from the head. Unconscious on the pavement. The truck bore no damage. The girl did not move.</description></item></channel></rss>