<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Events on Crash Count</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/</link><description>Recent content in Events on Crash Count</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://crashcountnyc.com/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>11-Year-Old Pedestrian Injured Crossing With Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4754640/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4754640/</guid><description>An 11-year-old girl suffered abrasions and lower leg injuries while crossing 7 Avenue at West 131 Street. She was conscious and obeying the crossing signal. The crash details lack driver error data, but the impact caused significant harm to a vulnerable pedestrian.</description></item><item><title>13-Year-Old Pedestrian Hit Crossing Against Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4799962/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4799962/</guid><description>A 13-year-old girl suffered a concussion after being struck by an SUV while crossing against the signal on East 125th Street in Manhattan. The SUV, traveling east, hit her with its right front bumper near a parked bus. The pedestrian was conscious but injured.</description></item><item><title>Acura Sedan Strikes Woman at Harlem Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4727559/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4727559/</guid><description>A southbound Acura hit a 57-year-old woman at Lexington and East 121st. Blood pooled. She stayed conscious. The sedan’s rear dented. The driver remained. Harlem bore silent witness. Steel and flesh collided in the crosswalk’s shadow.</description></item><item><title>Aggressive Driving Causes Multi-Vehicle Crash Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4783342/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4783342/</guid><description>Two sedans collided on West 127th Street in Manhattan during a police pursuit. The driver of one vehicle suffered back injuries and bruising. Police cite aggressive driving and driver distraction as key factors in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Alcohol-Fueled Midnight Multi-Car Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4784020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4784020/</guid><description>Four vehicles collide at midnight on W 134th and Adam Clayton Powell Jr Blvd. Steel twists, glass shatters. Three men, belted in, suffer crushed necks and torn flesh. Sirens wail as blood pools on cold asphalt, the city’s silence shattered by chaos.</description></item><item><title>Ambulance Rear-Ends Taxi on West 125 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4723395/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4723395/</guid><description>An ambulance struck the right rear bumper of a southbound taxi on West 125 Street in Manhattan. The taxi driver, a 38-year-old man, suffered a head injury and was left in shock. The crash was caused by the ambulance following too closely.</description></item><item><title>Bicyclist Ejected, Head Injured on Saint Nicholas Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4710345/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4710345/</guid><description>A 23-year-old male bicyclist was ejected and suffered a head contusion on Saint Nicholas Avenue. The rider was conscious but injured, with no safety equipment used. The crash involved a single bike traveling north, impacting front center and causing serious injury.</description></item><item><title>Bicyclist Ejected, Suffers Head Injury in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734940/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734940/</guid><description>A 37-year-old male bicyclist was ejected and suffered a head injury at Madison Avenue in Manhattan. The cyclist sustained a concussion and was seriously injured. The crash involved a single bike traveling north, with unspecified contributing factors noted by police.</description></item><item><title>Bicyclist Injured After Vehicle Passes Too Closely</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4796221/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4796221/</guid><description>A 40-year-old male bicyclist suffered elbow and lower arm injuries after a vehicle passed too closely on W 128 St in Manhattan. The impact caused whiplash and left front bumper damage to the vehicle. The cyclist was not ejected and was riding northbound.</description></item><item><title>Bicyclist Injured in Ambulance Rear-End Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4798880/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4798880/</guid><description>A bicyclist struck the back of a parked ambulance in Manhattan’s 10037 zip code. The impact caused head injuries and bruising. Police cited unsafe speed as a contributing factor. The cyclist was conscious and not ejected from the bike.</description></item><item><title>Bicyclist Injured in Manhattan U-Turn Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4751670/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4751670/</guid><description>A 20-year-old male bicyclist suffered neck injuries and shock after a collision with a vehicle making a U-turn in Manhattan. The impact struck the bike’s right front bumper and the vehicle’s left front quarter panel. Driver errors contributed to the crash.</description></item><item><title>Bicyclist Injured in Rear-End Collision on West 142 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4735135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4735135/</guid><description>A bicyclist was ejected and injured in a rear-end collision on West 142 Street in Manhattan. The crash involved a Chevrolet SUV and a bike traveling eastbound. The bicyclist suffered abrasions and lower leg injuries.</description></item><item><title>Bicyclist Injured in Southbound Collision on West 146 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4719495/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4719495/</guid><description>A 10-year-old boy riding a bike southbound on West 146 Street was injured in a collision. The police report lists unspecified contributing factors but does not identify driver errors or victim fault. The child was not ejected and suffered shock and injury.</description></item><item><title>Broken Pavement Throws Teen Cyclist Headfirst</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4751696/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4751696/</guid><description>A teenage boy riding east on West 125th struck broken pavement and was hurled headfirst onto concrete. Blood pooled. He lay semiconscious, bleeding from the head. Sirens wailed. The city’s fractured streets claimed another young rider.</description></item><item><title>Bus and Sedan Collision Injures Passenger</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4738206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4738206/</guid><description>A bus and sedan collided on West 125 Street in Manhattan. The impact injured a 36-year-old male passenger, causing shoulder and upper arm contusions. The crash involved driver inattention and inexperience, highlighting critical driver errors behind the collision.</description></item><item><title>Bus Backing Unsafely Hits Sedan on West 154 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724125/</guid><description>A bus backing unsafely struck a sedan traveling north on West 154 Street. The sedan’s driver and front passenger suffered back injuries and bruises. The bus was making a U-turn when its right front bumper collided with the sedan’s left side doors.</description></item><item><title>Bus Collides with Bicyclist on West 124 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4766617/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4766617/</guid><description>A bus traveling south struck a bicyclist heading east on West 124 Street in Manhattan. The cyclist, a 37-year-old woman, suffered knee and lower leg abrasions. Police report no vehicle damage and list unspecified contributing factors without victim fault.</description></item><item><title>Bus Crushes E-Bike Rider on Lenox Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4789910/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4789910/</guid><description>A city bus struck a 59-year-old man on an e-bike at Lenox Avenue and West 138th Street. His head was crushed. He died there, unconscious, in the dark, while the city slept. The street claimed another life.</description></item><item><title>Bus Hits Pedestrian Playing in Manhattan Roadway</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4703058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4703058/</guid><description>A 62-year-old man suffered knee and lower leg injuries after a bus struck him on East 125 Street. The impact came from the bus’s left front bumper. Driver inattention and distraction caused the collision at a busy intersection.</description></item><item><title>Bus Makes Left Turn, Hits Parked Sedan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4717053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4717053/</guid><description>A bus turning left struck a parked sedan on West 125 Street in Manhattan. The sedan driver suffered shock but no severe injury. Police cited driver inattention and distraction as contributing factors in the crash, highlighting systemic dangers in vehicle operation.</description></item><item><title>Bus Strikes Bicyclist on 7th Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4721198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4721198/</guid><description>A bicyclist suffered head injuries after a bus struck him on 7th Avenue in Manhattan. The crash occurred at 6:06 p.m. The bus was parked when the collision happened. Driver inattention was cited as a contributing factor in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Bus Strikes Bicyclist Passing on West 125th</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744201/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744201/</guid><description>A bicyclist suffered knee and lower leg abrasions after a bus collided with his bike’s rear on West 125th Street. The bus was traveling westbound, striking the cyclist who was passing improperly amid debris, according to the police report.</description></item><item><title>Bus Turns Right, Injures Bicyclist on East 125 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4710335/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4710335/</guid><description>A city bus making a right turn struck a 17-year-old bicyclist traveling east on East 125 Street. The cyclist was partially ejected and sustained abrasions to his elbow and lower arm. The bus driver’s failure to maintain safe distance caused the collision.</description></item><item><title>Chain-Reaction Crash on Harlem River Drive</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4793563/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4793563/</guid><description>Three men suffered injuries in a multi-vehicle collision on Harlem River Drive. Two SUVs and a sedan collided while traveling southbound. Police cite following too closely as the cause. Injuries ranged from neck to full-body trauma, all conscious and not ejected.</description></item><item><title>Council Member Yusef Salaam Throws Support Behind Albany Push To Rein In Speeding Drivers</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/press-2025-04-30t00-00-00-00-00/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/press-2025-04-30t00-00-00-00-00/</guid><description>Council Member Yusef Salaam is using his lived experience to move towards the ultimate North Star of street safety: holding repeatedly reckless drivers accountable.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Causes Sedan Collision in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4786821/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4786821/</guid><description>Two sedans collided near West 129th Street in Manhattan. The female driver of one vehicle suffered back injuries and whiplash. Police cited driver inattention and distraction as the cause. Impact occurred on the left rear quarter panel and right front bumper.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Causes SUV-Sedan Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4696151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4696151/</guid><description>A 33-year-old female driver suffered back injuries and whiplash when her sedan collided with an SUV on West 135 Street. The crash occurred during a left turn, with driver inattention cited as a key factor in the impact and injuries.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Crashes Into Parked SUVs</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4801341/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4801341/</guid><description>A distracted driver traveling east collided with multiple parked SUVs on Central Park North in Manhattan. The impact overturned the moving vehicle and injured the driver, who suffered a head abrasion. The crash exposed dangers of driver inattention and improper lane use.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Ejects Skater in Manhattan Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4775703/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4775703/</guid><description>A 46-year-old female skater was ejected and injured after a collision involving a sedan and an electric scooter in Manhattan. The driver’s inattention and inexperience caused the crash, resulting in abrasions and lower leg injuries.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Fails to Yield, Injures Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4720964/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4720964/</guid><description>A bicyclist was ejected and suffered a head injury after a vehicle making a U-turn struck him on Lenox Avenue. The crash, caused by driver inattention and failure to yield right-of-way, left the cyclist bruised but conscious.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Hits Bicyclist on West 145 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4708949/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4708949/</guid><description>A 36-year-old male bicyclist was injured in Manhattan after colliding with a parked SUV. The crash occurred at 5:47 AM on West 145 Street. The bicyclist suffered abrasions to his elbow and lower arm. Driver inattention caused the impact.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Hits Manhattan Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4716138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4716138/</guid><description>A bicyclist was injured and ejected after a collision with a vehicle on West 121 Street in Manhattan. The driver’s inattention caused the crash, striking the cyclist’s center back end. The rider suffered facial injuries and minor bleeding.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Hits Manhattan Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4730569/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4730569/</guid><description>A 44-year-old male bicyclist was ejected and injured in a Manhattan crash. The collision involved driver inattention and unsafe speed. The rider suffered abrasions and lower leg injuries while wearing a helmet. The crash exposed critical dangers from distracted driving.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Hits Manhattan Pedestrian</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4759276/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4759276/</guid><description>A distracted driver making a left turn struck a 36-year-old man crossing Saint Nicholas Avenue with the signal. The pedestrian suffered hip and upper leg contusions. The crash exposed failure to yield and driver inattention at a busy intersection.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Hits Pedestrian at Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4716108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4716108/</guid><description>A distracted driver struck a 38-year-old man crossing West 145 Street in Manhattan. The pedestrian suffered a head injury and concussion. The impact occurred at the vehicle’s center front end, causing serious harm at a busy intersection.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Hits Pedestrian Crossing Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4728062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4728062/</guid><description>A 73-year-old man crossing West 125 Street with the signal was struck by a vehicle traveling east. The pedestrian sustained abrasions to his elbow and lower arm. Driver inattention caused the collision, leaving the victim injured but conscious.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Hits Pedestrian on West 130 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4754152/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4754152/</guid><description>A 34-year-old man walking along West 130 Street was struck by a Jeep SUV. The driver’s inattention and following too closely caused the collision. The pedestrian suffered bruises and an elbow injury but remained conscious at the scene.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Strikes Manhattan Pedestrian</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731631/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731631/</guid><description>A 37-year-old woman crossing 7 Avenue in Manhattan suffered knee and lower leg injuries after a distracted driver hit her. The impact left bruises and contusions, highlighting the dangers of driver inattention on city streets late at night.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Driver Strikes Pedestrian on 8 Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744798/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744798/</guid><description>A sedan driver distracted by inattention struck a male pedestrian at an intersection on 8 Avenue in Manhattan. The pedestrian suffered severe full-body injuries and was rendered unconscious. The vehicle showed no damage despite the serious impact.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Drivers Cause Manhattan E-Bike Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4712719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4712719/</guid><description>Two cyclists collided on West 122 Street in Manhattan. Both were riding straight when driver inattention led to impact. One rider suffered bruises and arm injuries. No vehicle damage was reported. Illegal drug use by one driver was noted by police.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Drivers Collide on West 124 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4729626/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4729626/</guid><description>Two vehicles collided on West 124 Street when both drivers were inattentive. The taxi traveling north and the SUV making a left turn struck each other, injuring both drivers and a rear passenger. Shoulder and head injuries resulted amid shock and pain complaints.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Sedan Hits Helmeted Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4766612/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4766612/</guid><description>A sedan driver’s inattention caused a collision with a helmeted 24-year-old bicyclist on West 124 Street in Manhattan. The cyclist suffered abrasions and injuries to his knee and lower leg. The sedan showed no damage, underscoring the impact on the vulnerable rider.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Sedan Veers, Slams Cyclist Head-First</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724593/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724593/</guid><description>A sedan veered at West 141st and St. Nicholas, striking a 22-year-old cyclist. The driver, distracted and failing to hold the lane, sent the rider flying. Blood pooled. The cyclist lay conscious, head bleeding, the bike twisted in the street.</description></item><item><title>Distracted SUV Driver Hits Bicyclist on Frederick Douglass Blvd</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4772278/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4772278/</guid><description>A distracted SUV driver struck a 25-year-old bicyclist on Frederick Douglass Blvd in Manhattan. The cyclist was partially ejected, suffering head abrasions. The SUV showed no damage despite the impact. Driver inattention was cited as the primary cause.</description></item><item><title>Distracted SUV Driver Hits Manhattan Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4787219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4787219/</guid><description>A distracted SUV driver struck a northbound bicyclist on Frederick Douglass Blvd in Manhattan. The 48-year-old woman suffered a fractured elbow and dislocation. The SUV was parked before impact, which hit the bike’s left front quarter panel.</description></item><item><title>Distracted SUV Driver Injures Self in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4705255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4705255/</guid><description>A 28-year-old man driving a Jeep SUV on East 121 Street in Manhattan suffered internal injuries after a crash. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s left front bumper was damaged. The driver was conscious and restrained by a lap belt and harness.</description></item><item><title>Distracted SUV Rear-Ends E-Bike Rider</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4746214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4746214/</guid><description>An SUV stopped in traffic struck an e-bike from behind on Lenox Avenue. The 24-year-old e-bike rider suffered knee and lower leg injuries. Police cited driver inattention as the primary cause. The e-bike operator was conscious and wearing a helmet.</description></item><item><title>Distracted SUV Strikes Pedestrian Crossing Outside Crosswalk</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744206/</guid><description>A 60-year-old woman suffered head injuries after a distracted SUV driver struck her while she crossed outside a crosswalk in Manhattan. The impact caused abrasions and left the pedestrian conscious but injured. Driver inattention was a key factor in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Distracted SUV Strikes Pedestrian on St Nicholas Ave</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4795404/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4795404/</guid><description>A 20-year-old woman suffered back abrasions after a northbound SUV struck her outside an intersection on St Nicholas Ave. The driver’s inattention caused the crash. The pedestrian was conscious but injured, highlighting the dangers of distracted driving in Manhattan.</description></item><item><title>Distracted Taxi Driver Collides with SUV in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804380/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804380/</guid><description>A distracted taxi driver merging on W 149 St struck a southbound SUV’s left rear quarter panel. The taxi’s right front quarter panel took the impact. The taxi driver suffered chest injuries and shock, with no ejection reported.</description></item><item><title>Driver Distraction Causes Multi-Vehicle Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734837/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734837/</guid><description>A distracted driver traveling east on West 145 St Bridge collided with multiple vehicles, injuring a 59-year-old male driver. Impact damaged left front and rear panels of involved vehicles. The injured driver suffered knee and lower leg bruises but remained conscious.</description></item><item><title>Driver Distraction Injures Pedestrian at Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724323/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724323/</guid><description>A pedestrian suffered a head injury after a vehicle struck them at the intersection of West 112 Street and 8 Avenue in Manhattan. The driver’s inattention caused the collision, leaving the victim in shock with serious injuries.</description></item><item><title>Driver Inattention Causes Manhattan Multi-Vehicle Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4738598/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4738598/</guid><description>A distracted driver starting from parking struck multiple parked vehicles on West 134 Street in Manhattan. The 82-year-old male driver suffered neck abrasions but was not ejected. The crash highlights the dangers of driver inattention amid dense urban traffic.</description></item><item><title>Driver Inattention Injures Two in Manhattan Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4803183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4803183/</guid><description>Metal crumpled and glass scattered on Bradhurst Avenue near West 142nd Street. Sirens cut through the night as two people, a driver and a front passenger, suffered head and chest injuries. Both remained conscious, shaken and hurt in the aftermath.</description></item><item><title>E-Bike Fails to Yield, Injures Manhattan Pedestrian</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4792164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4792164/</guid><description>An e-bike traveling north on Lenox Avenue struck a 39-year-old pedestrian crossing with the signal. The pedestrian suffered knee and lower leg contusions. According to the police report, the e-bike driver failed to yield right-of-way, causing the collision.</description></item><item><title>E-Bike Rider Injured in Sedan Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4700325/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4700325/</guid><description>An e-bike rider suffered severe leg injuries after a collision with a southbound sedan on East 132 Street. The bike struck the sedan’s left front quarter panel. The rider remained conscious but sustained fractures and dislocations to the lower leg.</description></item><item><title>E-Bike Strikes Pedestrian Working in Roadway</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4755201/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4755201/</guid><description>An e-bike traveling west on West 155 Street struck a 34-year-old male pedestrian working in the roadway. The pedestrian suffered a fractured and dislocated elbow and lower arm. The collision involved unsafe speed and aggressive driving by the e-bike operator.</description></item><item><title>E-Scooter Collides with Sedan During Improper Turn</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4752188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4752188/</guid><description>A 24-year-old e-scooter driver suffered upper arm injuries after a collision with a sedan turning improperly on West 111 Street in Manhattan. The impact struck the scooter’s front and the sedan’s right side, highlighting dangerous turning maneuvers.</description></item><item><title>E-Scooter Driver Injured in Sedan Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4742583/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4742583/</guid><description>An e-scooter driver suffered a severe leg injury after a collision with a sedan on Madison Avenue. The scooter rider was partially ejected and fractured his knee and lower leg. The sedan showed no damage despite impact to its right front quarter panel.</description></item><item><title>Elderly Pedestrian Struck by Backing Sedan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744947/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744947/</guid><description>A 74-year-old woman crossing East 135 Street away from an intersection was struck by a backing BMW sedan. The impact caused a hip and upper leg injury, leaving her bruised but conscious. The driver reversed into the pedestrian, causing serious harm.</description></item><item><title>Garbage Truck Hits Pedestrian at Harlem Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4810121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4810121/</guid><description>A garbage truck turned right on West 145th. The driver did not see the man working in the street. Metal struck flesh. The pedestrian went down, hurt in the leg. The truck rolled on. The street stayed cold and hard.</description></item><item><title>Harlem grandmother killed by shooter’s stray bullet remembered as local business pioneer</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/press-2025-04-24t00-00-00-00-00/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/press-2025-04-24t00-00-00-00-00/</guid><description>Harlem residents are in mourning on Thursday over the shooting death this week of a grandmother and local business pioneer, struck down with a stray bullet. Excenia Mette, 61, was fatally gunned down at around 10:30 p.m. on April 22 along West 113th Street and Lenox Avenue. Police say Mette overheard a barrage of gunfire erupt and she&amp;hellip; Read More</description></item><item><title>Improper Lane Use Injures Manhattan Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4754644/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4754644/</guid><description>A 48-year-old bicyclist was ejected and injured with abrasions and shoulder trauma after a sedan’s improper lane usage in Manhattan. The crash caused no vehicle damage but left the cyclist hurt and conscious, highlighting dangerous driver behavior.</description></item><item><title>Inexperienced Driver Hits Bicyclist in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4740576/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4740576/</guid><description>A bicyclist was injured and ejected after colliding with a stationary SUV in Manhattan. The SUV driver’s inexperience contributed to the crash. The cyclist suffered bruises and arm injuries, remaining conscious despite the impact on the vehicle’s left side doors.</description></item><item><title>Inexperienced Driver Hits Pedestrian Crossing Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4785197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4785197/</guid><description>A 75-year-old woman suffered knee and lower leg injuries after being struck by a sedan on West 135th Street. The driver failed to yield right-of-way, causing a collision at the intersection. The pedestrian was conscious and crossing with the signal.</description></item><item><title>KIA Sedan Hits Debris, Slams Parked Car</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4805393/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4805393/</guid><description>Metal screeched on Harlem River Drive at 2:20 a.m. A KIA sedan struck debris while changing lanes and crashed into a parked Hyundai. A woman behind the wheel sat stunned. Five others, belted and bruised, stared into the darkness.</description></item><item><title>Manhattan Pedestrian Injured by Sedan Impact</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4737113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4737113/</guid><description>A 60-year-old man crossing outside a crosswalk was struck by a sedan traveling east on East 125th Street. The impact to his lower leg caused abrasions and injury. The driver continued straight, hitting the pedestrian with the right front bumper.</description></item><item><title>Manhattan Sedan Crash Injures Driver with Alcohol Involvement</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4795405/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4795405/</guid><description>A 22-year-old male driver suffered head injuries and incoherence after a northbound sedan crash in Manhattan. The vehicle’s front center was damaged. Alcohol involvement was cited as a contributing factor, with the driver using a permit license and deploying the airbag.</description></item><item><title>Moped Driver Ejected in Harlem Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4806799/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4806799/</guid><description>A moped slammed into the rear of an SUV on Frederick Douglass Boulevard. The impact threw the 35-year-old driver onto the street. Blood pooled near his head. Sirens echoed as first responders arrived. The man was conscious but bruised and shaken.</description></item><item><title>Moped Driver Ejected, Knee Injured on W 140 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4793607/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4793607/</guid><description>A 25-year-old moped driver was ejected and suffered knee and lower leg injuries on W 140 St in Manhattan. The crash caused contusions and bruises. The driver held a permit license and was traveling south when the impact occurred at the front center of the vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Moped Hits Elderly Pedestrian on West 132 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4710684/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4710684/</guid><description>A moped traveling southwest struck a 72-year-old woman on West 132 Street in Manhattan. The pedestrian suffered neck injuries and minor bleeding. The crash was caused by driver inattention and distraction, according to the police report.</description></item><item><title>Moped Strikes Bicyclist on 8th Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4759382/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4759382/</guid><description>A moped collided head-on with a bicyclist traveling south on 8th Avenue in Manhattan. The bicyclist suffered elbow and lower arm injuries and minor bleeding. Driver inattention was cited as a contributing factor in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Motorcycle Driver Ejected During Left Turn</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4722697/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4722697/</guid><description>A female motorcyclist was ejected and suffered severe whole-body injuries after a left turn on East 129 Street. Limited view contributed to the crash, causing impact to the motorcycle’s left front bumper. The rider was conscious but injured internally.</description></item><item><title>Motorcycle Hits Parked Sedan, Driver Partially Ejected</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4717748/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4717748/</guid><description>A motorcycle traveling west struck a parked sedan on West 117 Street in Manhattan. The motorcycle driver, a 27-year-old man, was partially ejected and suffered a head contusion. Police cite driver inattention as the primary contributing factor.</description></item><item><title>Motorcycle Injured in SUV Right-Turn Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4752718/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4752718/</guid><description>A motorcycle rider was partially ejected and injured in a collision with an SUV making a right turn on Madison Avenue. The crash involved following too closely and disregarding traffic control, causing severe arm injuries and bruising to the motorcyclist.</description></item><item><title>Motorcycle Passes Too Close, Passenger Injured</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804872/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804872/</guid><description>Metal grinds on Lenox Avenue near West 142nd. A motorcycle, southbound, edges too near. Sirens wail. A helmeted woman does not rise; her leg bruised. The street holds the echo of impact. The morning air is sharp with noise.</description></item><item><title>Motorcycle Rider Partially Ejected in Sedan Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744000/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4744000/</guid><description>A motorcycle traveling south on West 150 Street collided with a sedan also heading south. The motorcyclist was partially ejected, suffering knee and lower leg injuries with minor bleeding. The sedan showed no damage. Driver errors remain unspecified.</description></item><item><title>Motorcyclist Killed in Harlem River Drive Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4712117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4712117/</guid><description>A motorcycle skids on slick Harlem River Drive pavement, slamming head-on into an SUV. The rider, helmeted, is thrown hard, suffering fatal head trauma. Blood stains the asphalt. The bike lies shattered. Morning breaks over a silent road.</description></item><item><title>Multiple Motorcycle Collision with SUV on Harlem River Drive</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4749824/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4749824/</guid><description>Two motorcycles collided with an SUV on Harlem River Drive. Both motorcycle drivers suffered injuries, including partial ejection and burns. Police cited improper passing and lane usage as contributing factors. The SUV driver was also injured but remained inside the vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured at Manhattan Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4730049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4730049/</guid><description>A 37-year-old man suffered head injuries and abrasions after being struck at a Manhattan intersection. The pedestrian was conscious and injured while in the roadway. The crash involved an unspecified vehicle. No driver errors or contributing factors were reported.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured by Jeep at Manhattan Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4760666/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4760666/</guid><description>A 28-year-old man was struck at a Manhattan intersection while crossing with the signal. The Jeep’s right front quarter panel hit him, causing knee and lower leg injuries. The pedestrian suffered shock and complained of pain and nausea.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured by Sedan Backing Unsafely</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4718295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4718295/</guid><description>A 40-year-old woman crossing at West 125th Street was struck by a sedan backing unsafely. The driver’s inattention caused a severe elbow injury. The vehicle showed no damage despite the impact, highlighting the hidden dangers of careless reversing in busy intersections.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured Crossing West 130th Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4699258/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4699258/</guid><description>A 56-year-old man was struck while crossing West 130th Street near Lenox Avenue. The pedestrian suffered a fractured knee and lower leg. The sedan involved showed no damage. Confusion by the pedestrian contributed to the crash, according to police.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured Crossing With Signal Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4771908/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4771908/</guid><description>A 19-year-old man suffered knee and lower leg injuries after being struck at an intersection while crossing with the signal. The vehicle, traveling north, impacted the pedestrian with its front center, causing contusions but no vehicle damage.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured Crossing With Signal on 8 Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4755661/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4755661/</guid><description>A 25-year-old man suffered knee and lower leg injuries while crossing 8 Avenue at West 125 Street. He was conscious and sustained abrasions. The police report notes no driver errors or contributing factors. The pedestrian crossed with the signal at the intersection.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured Crossing with Signal on W 135 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4789649/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4789649/</guid><description>A 57-year-old woman suffered hip and upper leg injuries after being struck by a westbound sedan on W 135 St. The driver disregarded traffic control and drove at unsafe speed, colliding with the pedestrian crossing legally at an intersection.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured Emerging From Parked Vehicle</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4704103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4704103/</guid><description>A 43-year-old man suffered abrasions and arm injuries after a pick-up truck struck him while he emerged from behind a parked vehicle in Manhattan. The truck hit the pedestrian with its front center, causing moderate injury and leaving the victim conscious.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured Emerging Near Parked SUV</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4778205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4778205/</guid><description>A 44-year-old man suffered knee and lower leg bruises after emerging from near a parked SUV on West 145th Street in Manhattan. The SUV, traveling west, struck him with its right front bumper. The pedestrian remained conscious despite injuries.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured in Manhattan Failure to Yield Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4770147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4770147/</guid><description>A 66-year-old man suffered chest contusions after a vehicle failed to yield at a Manhattan intersection. The pedestrian was crossing with the signal when struck. The driver’s failure to yield right-of-way caused the impact and injury.</description></item><item><title>Pedestrian Injured in Manhattan SUV Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4751387/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4751387/</guid><description>A 35-year-old man suffered abrasions and arm injuries after being struck by an SUV on West 145 Street in Manhattan. The vehicle was parked before impact. The pedestrian remained conscious amid the chaotic scene of colliding vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Rear-End Collision Injures Three in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4752716/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4752716/</guid><description>Two sedans traveling east on East 125 Street collided in a rear-end crash. Three occupants suffered whiplash and full-body injuries. The impact struck the center back end of the lead vehicle. Following too closely caused the crash, police report states.</description></item><item><title>Salaam co-sponsors bill boosting street safety by curbing repeat speeders.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/140-sponsors-7866/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/140-sponsors-7866/</guid><description>Council calls for speed limiters in cars of repeat speeders. The resolution urges Albany to pass S.7621/A.7979. The measure targets reckless drivers. It aims to cut deadly crashes. The bill sits in committee. Streets remain dangerous.</description></item><item><title>Salaam co-sponsors bill closing enforcement loophole, boosting pedestrian and cyclist safety.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/130-sponsors-7866/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/130-sponsors-7866/</guid><description>Council wants VINs on tickets when plates vanish or hide. Lawbreakers dodge cameras with covered plates. Cops seize thousands of these cars. Current law lets violators slip away. The bill aims to close that loophole. Committee delays action.</description></item><item><title>Salaam co-sponsors bill reducing commercial parking time, boosting street safety.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/104-sponsors-7866/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/104-sponsors-7866/</guid><description>Council bill Int 1069-2024 slashes legal parking time for tractor-trailers and similar trucks to 90 minutes. Commercial vehicles clogging curbs will face tighter limits. The measure targets streets where hulking rigs linger, blocking sightlines and endangering walkers and riders.</description></item><item><title>Salaam co-sponsors bill to boost step street lighting, improving pedestrian safety.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/62-sponsors-7866/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/62-sponsors-7866/</guid><description>Council wants lights on city step streets. The bill orders the DOT to brighten at least 25 stairways a year. Dark stairs mean danger. Light means fewer falls, fewer hidden threats. The push comes from a broad coalition. The goal is simple: safer steps.</description></item><item><title>Salaam co-sponsors cool pavement pilot bill with no safety impact.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/41-sponsors-7866/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/41-sponsors-7866/</guid><description>Council wants DOT to test cool pavement in four heat-vulnerable, disadvantaged neighborhoods. The pilot aims to fight the city’s heat island effect. The bill sits in committee. No direct impact on pedestrian or cyclist safety. Streets stay hot. Danger remains.</description></item><item><title>Salaam co-sponsors study of alternative public transit fare systems.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/73-sponsors-7866/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/73-sponsors-7866/</guid><description>Council pulled the plug on a bill to study new transit fare systems. The plan never left committee. No action, no change. Riders keep paying the same way. Streets stay the same. The city missed a chance to rethink how people move.</description></item><item><title>Salaam sponsors pilot for high-visibility pavement markings, boosting street safety.</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/69-sponsors-7866/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/69-sponsors-7866/</guid><description>Council moves to test bold pavement markings at crash sites. Five spots per borough. Focus: places where drivers have killed or hurt the most. The city must report back. The law dies when the pilot ends. Streets remember every scar.</description></item><item><title>Scooter Rider Killed Fleeing Traffic Stop</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/press-2025-03-06t00-00-00-00-00/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/press-2025-03-06t00-00-00-00-00/</guid><description>A stolen minivan tore through Harlem. The driver ran from police. He struck Devon Hughley on a scooter. Hughley died at Harlem Hospital. The driver fled. Police used facial recognition. They arrested Enesin Delarosa. Grief lingers. Memorials remain.</description></item><item><title>Sedan and E-Scooter Collide on Madison Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4695027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4695027/</guid><description>A sedan traveling north struck an eastbound e-scooter on Madison Avenue. The e-scooter driver, unlicensed and distracted, suffered a fractured knee and dislocation. The sedan driver was licensed but inattentive. Impact damaged both vehicles’ front ends.</description></item><item><title>Sedan and Moped Collide on Saint Nicholas Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4699165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4699165/</guid><description>A sedan and moped collided on Saint Nicholas Avenue, injuring the sedan driver. The driver suffered neck injuries and whiplash. Police cite traffic control disregard and unsafe speed as key factors in the crash. Both vehicles sustained front-end damage.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Backing Into Parked Bus Injures Child Passenger</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4739229/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4739229/</guid><description>A sedan backing unsafely struck a parked bus in Manhattan’s 9th Council district. A 7-year-old girl, secured in the rear seat, suffered back injuries and shock. Driver distraction and unsafe backing caused the crash, leaving the child in pain and nausea.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Collision Injures Manhattan Driver</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4739240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4739240/</guid><description>A driver suffered neck injuries in a multi-sedan crash at West 129 Street. Police cite driver inattention and distraction as key factors. The injured driver, conscious and restrained by a lap belt, experienced whiplash but was not ejected from the vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Collision Injures Rear Passenger on W 135 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4772846/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4772846/</guid><description>Two sedans collided on W 135 St in Manhattan. The impact struck the left rear bumper of one vehicle and the right front bumper of the other. A 29-year-old male passenger suffered head abrasions and shock, remaining inside the vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Collision on E 135 St Injures Driver</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4809272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4809272/</guid><description>Metal crumpled on E 135 St near Madison Ave. A sedan’s front end struck another car’s rear bumper. One man, 35, behind the wheel, suffered whiplash. Sirens echoed as responders arrived. The air was thick with the smell of gasoline and dust.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Collision on Harlem River Drive Ramp</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4785587/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4785587/</guid><description>Two sedans collided on the Harlem River Drive ramp. One driver suffered neck injuries and whiplash. The crash involved unsafe lane changing, striking the left rear bumper of one vehicle with the right front bumper of the other.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Driver Injured in Close-Passing Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4789072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4789072/</guid><description>A sedan driver suffered neck injuries after a box truck passed too closely in Manhattan. The crash caused whiplash but no ejection. Police cited the truck driver’s failure to maintain safe distance as the key factor in the collision.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Driver Injured in Left Turn Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4719487/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4719487/</guid><description>A sedan driver suffered knee and lower leg injuries after a collision during a left turn on West 136 Street. The crash caused abrasions and shock. Police cited driver inattention and distraction as contributing factors in the impact.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Driver Injured in Manhattan Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4800198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4800198/</guid><description>A Manhattan crash on W 125 St injured a 28-year-old sedan driver. The driver suffered knee and lower leg injuries and whiplash. Police cited outside car distraction and a defective accelerator as contributing factors in the collision.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Driver Loses Consciousness, Crashes in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4699707/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4699707/</guid><description>A 36-year-old male sedan driver lost consciousness while driving westbound in Manhattan. The vehicle struck a parked bus and a parked sedan. The driver was injured and in shock, restrained by a lap belt and harness. The crash caused front and side damage to vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Driver Strikes Cyclist on Lenox Ave</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4807737/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4807737/</guid><description>A sedan turning right on Lenox Avenue hit a cyclist riding straight on West 135th Street. The impact left the cyclist, a 45-year-old woman, conscious but with abrasions and a leg injury. Sirens echoed as bystanders gathered around the scene.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Driver Suffers Whiplash in Manhattan Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4762844/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4762844/</guid><description>A 56-year-old man driving a sedan in Manhattan suffered neck injuries and whiplash. The vehicle struck an object or another vehicle with its right front bumper. The driver was conscious and restrained but injured in the collision.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Hits Bicyclist on East 131 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4721033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4721033/</guid><description>A sedan struck a 24-year-old male bicyclist traveling west on East 131 Street in Manhattan. The cyclist suffered knee and lower leg abrasions. The crash occurred as the sedan driver, heading south, failed to maintain attention, causing the collision.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Hits Bicyclist on Park Avenue Side</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4740999/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4740999/</guid><description>A sedan traveling north struck a westbound bicyclist on Park Avenue in Manhattan. The bicyclist was ejected and suffered neck abrasions. The driver was using a hand-held cell phone, contributing to the crash. The cyclist was unlicensed and unhelmeted.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Hits Front Passenger, Causes Serious Injury</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4786825/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4786825/</guid><description>A sedan traveling east on W 135 St struck its front passenger, causing a severe hip and upper leg injury. The passenger was unconscious and restrained by a lap belt. Driver distraction was cited as a contributing factor in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Hits Pedestrian Getting On Vehicle</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4732578/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4732578/</guid><description>A 36-year-old man suffered upper arm injuries after a sedan struck him while he was getting on a vehicle outside an intersection in Manhattan. The driver failed to yield right-of-way, causing the collision and leaving the pedestrian in shock with pain and nausea.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Rear-Ends ATV Passenger Injuries</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731451/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731451/</guid><description>A sedan struck the rear of an open-body ATV on East 119 Street in Manhattan. Two elderly passengers suffered neck injuries and shock. Police cited alcohol involvement and aggressive driving by the ATV driver as contributing factors. Both vehicles traveled southbound.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Rear-Ends Box Truck on West 145 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4714578/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4714578/</guid><description>A sedan struck a box truck from behind on West 145 Street, injuring the sedan driver. The impact damaged the sedan’s right front quarter panel and the truck’s left front bumper. Driver distraction and tailgating caused the crash.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Rear-Ends Pickup Truck on Harlem River Drive</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4782608/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4782608/</guid><description>A sedan collided into the rear of a pickup truck on Harlem River Drive, demolishing the sedan&amp;rsquo;s rear. The sedan driver, a 45-year-old man, suffered upper arm injuries and shock. Police cite driver inexperience and other vehicular factors as causes.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Bicyclist During Left Turn</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4720798/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4720798/</guid><description>A sedan making a left turn collided with a southbound bicyclist on West 153 Street in Manhattan. The bicyclist suffered a head injury and concussion. Police report cites pedestrian/bicyclist confusion as a contributing factor, highlighting driver error in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Bicyclist During Left Turn in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4716181/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4716181/</guid><description>A sedan making a left turn hit a northbound bicyclist on West 114 Street. The 23-year-old cyclist suffered abrasions to his elbow and lower arm. Driver inattention and bicyclist confusion contributed to the collision in a busy Manhattan corridor.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Bicyclist Making Left Turn</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4772447/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4772447/</guid><description>A sedan traveling west collided head-on with a bicyclist making a left turn eastbound on W 116 St. The 19-year-old cyclist was ejected and suffered severe leg fractures. Driver inattention and inexperience contributed to the crash.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Bicyclist on Saint Nicholas Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4730335/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4730335/</guid><description>A 36-year-old bicyclist was ejected and suffered severe chest injuries after a collision with a sedan traveling west on Saint Nicholas Avenue. The impact occurred at the bike&amp;rsquo;s front center and the sedan&amp;rsquo;s left front bumper, causing fractures and dislocations.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Bicyclist Starting from Parking</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734741/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734741/</guid><description>A sedan driver distracted by inattention struck a bicyclist traveling west on West 132 Street in Manhattan. The cyclist was partially ejected, suffering upper arm and shoulder injuries and incoherence. The crash exposed dangers from driver distraction and medication effects.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Cyclist on Adam Clayton Powell Jr Blvd</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4805281/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4805281/</guid><description>Evening traffic on Adam Clayton Powell Jr Blvd broke with the sound of metal and shouts. A BMW sedan’s right front bumper collided with a northbound cyclist, leaving the rider bruised and clutching his arm on the pavement of W 140 St.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes E-Scooter on West 130th Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4808223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4808223/</guid><description>A sedan collided with an e-scooter at West 130th Street and 5th Avenue. The e-scooter driver, a 38-year-old man, was ejected and suffered a head contusion. Sirens echoed as first responders arrived. The street bore fresh skid marks and broken plastic.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Pedestrian Crossing Against Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4741341/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4741341/</guid><description>A sedan traveling east on West 145 Street hit a pedestrian crossing against the signal. The man suffered head injuries and incoherence, bleeding minorly. The crash happened off intersection near Saint Nicholas Avenue in Manhattan’s 10030 zip code.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Pedestrian Crossing Outside Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4802473/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4802473/</guid><description>A sedan traveling west struck an 18-year-old pedestrian crossing outside an intersection in East Harlem. The pedestrian suffered a facial injury and concussion but remained conscious. The vehicle showed no damage, highlighting the severity of impact despite low visible harm.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Pedestrian Crossing With Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4714792/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4714792/</guid><description>A 42-year-old man was injured crossing West 135 Street at an intersection. A BMW sedan making a left turn struck him, causing abrasions and lower leg injuries. The driver failed to yield and was inattentive, according to the police report.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Pedestrian Crossing With Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4719135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4719135/</guid><description>A 34-year-old man suffered a fractured leg after a sedan failed to yield while making a left turn. The pedestrian was crossing with the signal at an intersection in Manhattan. The driver’s failure to yield caused severe lower leg injuries.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Pedestrian Crossing With Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4778353/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4778353/</guid><description>A 47-year-old man suffered knee and lower leg injuries after a sedan traveling south on Lexington Avenue struck him at an intersection. The pedestrian was crossing with the signal. The vehicle showed no damage despite the impact.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Pedestrian Playing on West 125 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4719713/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4719713/</guid><description>A 26-year-old woman suffered bruises and arm injuries after a sedan hit her while she played in the roadway. The driver, traveling west, impacted the pedestrian with the vehicle’s left front bumper, causing shock and contusions.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Strikes Pedestrians Crossing With Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4810119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4810119/</guid><description>A sedan turned right on Lenox Avenue. It hit a woman and a child crossing with the signal. The woman suffered a bruised leg. The child’s injuries were not specified. The driver failed to yield. The street stayed busy. The danger stayed real.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Turning Improperly Injures Rear Passenger</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4707022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4707022/</guid><description>A sedan making a left turn struck another sedan traveling north on West 141 Street. The impact injured a 46-year-old male rear passenger with neck whiplash. The driver’s improper turning caused the collision, leaving the passenger conscious but hurt.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Turns Left, Hits E-Scooter Rider</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4773130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4773130/</guid><description>A sedan making a left turn struck a 14-year-old e-scooter rider traveling north on W 130 St. The rider suffered facial contusions and bruises. Police cited driver inattention, traffic control disregard, and unsafe speed as contributing factors in the collision.</description></item><item><title>Sedan Turns Left, Strikes Pedestrian at Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4708232/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4708232/</guid><description>A sedan turning left struck a 60-year-old woman crossing with the signal on West 122 Street. The pedestrian suffered a fractured knee and lower leg injuries. The driver’s inattention and improper turning caused the collision late at night in Manhattan.</description></item><item><title>Sedan’s Wide Turn Hurls E-Scooter Rider Headfirst</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4725932/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4725932/</guid><description>A sedan swung wide on West 155th. An e-scooter rider, straight ahead, collided and flew. Blood pooled on the blacktop. The man, gasping, lay conscious, his skull split. Driver inattention and unsafe lane change carved the night.</description></item><item><title>Slain NYC bodega-owner, grandma senselessly gunned down remembered as ‘Mayor of Harlem’ as mourners rail against NYC gun violence</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/press-2025-04-26t00-00-00-00-00/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/press-2025-04-26t00-00-00-00-00/</guid><description>Family and friends of beloved Harlem bodega owner and grandmother who was fatally shot in a hail of bullets meant for someone else this week – marched to the site of the 61-year-old’s death chanting “Say her name, Momma Zee” Saturday and remembering her as the &amp;ldquo;Mayor of Harlem.&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>SUV and Bus Collide During Improper Passing Maneuver</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4702362/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4702362/</guid><description>A 27-year-old passenger suffered knee and lower leg injuries when an SUV and a bus collided on East 135 Street. The crash occurred amid improper lane usage as both vehicles attempted left turns, striking each other’s front and rear quarters.</description></item><item><title>SUV and Sedan Collide on East 123rd Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4787156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4787156/</guid><description>A westbound SUV and southbound sedan collided at East 123rd Street and Park Avenue. The SUV driver’s inattention and inexperience caused the crash. A 29-year-old female passenger suffered knee and lower leg injuries, bruised but conscious and not ejected.</description></item><item><title>SUV and Sedan Collide on Frederick Douglass Blvd</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4784976/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4784976/</guid><description>A northbound SUV and eastbound sedan crashed at Frederick Douglass Blvd and W 122 St. The SUV driver suffered a concussion and head injury. Police cite traffic control disregard as the cause. Both vehicles sustained front-end damage.</description></item><item><title>SUV and Sedan Collide on W 135 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4796222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4796222/</guid><description>Two vehicles struck on W 135 St in Manhattan. The SUV’s right side doors were hit by the sedan’s front end. Both male drivers and a front passenger suffered head injuries and whiplash. The crash caused serious trauma without ejection or loss of consciousness.</description></item><item><title>SUV and Taxi Collide on W 116 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4768326/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4768326/</guid><description>A northbound SUV struck by a westbound taxi on W 116 St caused injuries to the SUV driver. The impact hit the SUV’s right side doors and the taxi’s left front bumper. Driver distraction and inexperience contributed to the crash.</description></item><item><title>SUV Collides with Sedan on 7 Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4737257/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4737257/</guid><description>A Tesla SUV struck the right side of a Hyundai sedan making a left turn on 7 Avenue in Manhattan. The sedan driver, a 23-year-old woman, suffered head injuries and whiplash. Police cited failure to yield and improper turning as causes.</description></item><item><title>SUV Disregards Signal, Cyclist Injured in Harlem</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4808381/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4808381/</guid><description>A cyclist’s face hit pavement at St Nicholas Avenue and West 141st Street. Sirens echoed as the man, conscious but bloodied, was ejected from his bike. Metal scraped asphalt. Traffic halted. The crash left the cyclist with abrasions and pain.</description></item><item><title>SUV Disregards Traffic Control, Injures Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4791526/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4791526/</guid><description>A 22-year-old bicyclist was ejected and suffered head abrasions after a collision with an SUV on West 125th Street. The SUV driver disregarded traffic control, striking the cyclist during a left turn. The crash left the cyclist injured but conscious.</description></item><item><title>SUV Driver Injured After Failing to Yield</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4714382/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4714382/</guid><description>A 27-year-old male SUV driver suffered back injuries and whiplash in Manhattan after failing to yield right-of-way. The crash involved driver inattention and distraction. The vehicle sustained front-end damage, highlighting systemic dangers in urban traffic flow.</description></item><item><title>SUV Driver Semiconscious After Manhattan Collision</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4740131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4740131/</guid><description>A 59-year-old male driver lost consciousness and became semiconscious after a crash involving multiple SUVs on Saint Nicholas Avenue. The impact damaged front and rear bumpers. Police report cites loss of consciousness as a key factor in the crash.</description></item><item><title>SUV Fails to Yield, Injures Pedestrian Crossing</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4802009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4802009/</guid><description>A northbound SUV making a left turn struck a pedestrian crossing with the signal on St Nicholas Ave. Both the driver and pedestrian suffered injuries. The driver’s failure to yield and inattention caused the collision, leaving the pedestrian bruised and shocked.</description></item><item><title>SUV Hits Elderly Pedestrian on Bradhurst Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4743005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4743005/</guid><description>A 74-year-old woman crossing Bradhurst Avenue away from an intersection was struck by a northbound SUV making a right turn. The pedestrian suffered bruises and arm injuries. The driver’s inattention caused the collision, leaving the victim injured but conscious.</description></item><item><title>SUV Hits Parked Car on Harlem River Drive</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804437/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804437/</guid><description>Metal screeches under headlights on Harlem River Drive. Three cars, one parked, collide in the night. A sixty-six-year-old woman grips her chest, stunned, while others sit silent. Broken bumpers glint as traffic flows past the wreckage.</description></item><item><title>SUV Hits Pedestrian Crossing Against Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4785498/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4785498/</guid><description>A 59-year-old man was struck by an eastbound SUV making a right turn on W 134 St. The pedestrian was unconscious with head injuries. Police cite driver inattention as a key factor in the collision at the intersection.</description></item><item><title>SUV Hits Pedestrian Crossing With Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4781696/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4781696/</guid><description>A 32-year-old woman was struck by an SUV while crossing with the signal at a Manhattan intersection. The driver, making a right turn, showed inattention and inexperience. The pedestrian suffered knee and lower leg injuries but remained conscious.</description></item><item><title>SUV Left Turn Strikes Pedestrian Crossing Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4701722/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4701722/</guid><description>A pedestrian crossing with the signal suffered a severe shoulder injury when a GMC SUV making a left turn struck her at a Manhattan intersection. Limited driver visibility contributed to the collision, leaving the pedestrian fractured and dislocated.</description></item><item><title>SUV Left-Turn Hits Sedan on 8 Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4735704/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4735704/</guid><description>An SUV making a left turn struck a sedan traveling east on 8 Avenue in Manhattan. The sedan driver, a 51-year-old woman, suffered shoulder and upper arm injuries and was in shock. The impact damaged the left side doors of the sedan.</description></item><item><title>SUV Merging Strikes E-Bike Rider in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4751733/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4751733/</guid><description>An SUV merging northbound collided with a northbound e-bike at 5 Avenue in Manhattan. The e-bike rider, a 33-year-old man, sustained abdominal and pelvic injuries. The SUV’s left front quarter panel struck the e-bike’s center front end, causing abrasions and moderate injury.</description></item><item><title>SUV Passenger Distraction Hits Manhattan Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4801588/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4801588/</guid><description>A bicyclist suffered a severe facial fracture after an SUV, stopped in traffic, struck him on the right side. The crash left the rider injured but conscious, highlighting the dangers of passenger distraction in urban traffic.</description></item><item><title>SUV Passenger Suffers Head Injury in Manhattan Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4735453/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4735453/</guid><description>A front-seat passenger in an SUV suffered a concussion after a collision on East 129 Street in Manhattan. The vehicle struck an object with its left front bumper. Passenger distraction contributed to the crash, leaving the occupant injured but conscious.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ended by Motorcycle on St Nicholas Pl</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4808389/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4808389/</guid><description>A motorcycle slammed into the back of an SUV on St Nicholas Place. The crash left both drivers injured—one with head abrasions, the other with whiplash. Sirens echoed as first responders arrived. Metal scraped pavement. Both drivers remained conscious at the scene.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Box Truck on West 138 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4749905/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4749905/</guid><description>A 41-year-old male SUV driver suffered knee and lower leg injuries after rear-ending a box truck while both vehicles traveled south on West 138 Street in Manhattan. The SUV sustained damage to its left rear quarter panel.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Parked Bus on Manhattan Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4790144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4790144/</guid><description>A westbound SUV struck the rear of a parked bus on W 130 St in Manhattan. The collision caused neck injuries to a front-seat passenger. Slippery pavement contributed to the crash, highlighting hazardous road conditions and driver control failures.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Parked Sedan on E 118 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4780133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4780133/</guid><description>A speeding SUV struck the rear of a parked sedan on East 118th Street in Manhattan. Two occupants in the SUV suffered neck injuries and concussions. The crash caused significant damage to both vehicles’ rear and front ends.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Parked Sedan on West 136 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4703792/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4703792/</guid><description>A northbound SUV struck a parked sedan on West 136 Street in Manhattan. The sedan’s left rear bumper was damaged. The SUV driver, a 59-year-old man, suffered neck injuries and whiplash, remaining semiconscious after the crash. Unsafe speed was cited.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Sedan on Bradhurst Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4715695/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4715695/</guid><description>A parked SUV was struck from behind by a sedan traveling south on Bradhurst Avenue. The front passenger in the SUV suffered shoulder and upper arm injuries, experiencing shock and whiplash. Alcohol involvement was cited as a contributing factor in the crash.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Sedan on East 119 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4710329/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4710329/</guid><description>A station wagon SUV struck a sedan from behind on East 119 Street. Two passengers in the sedan suffered neck and back injuries, including whiplash. The crash was caused by the SUV following too closely, according to the police report.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Sedan on Madison Ave Bridge</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4769689/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4769689/</guid><description>A distracted SUV driver rear-ended a sedan stopped in traffic on Madison Ave Bridge. Two passengers suffered head injuries and whiplash. Both were conscious and restrained. The SUV’s left rear bumper struck the sedan’s front, causing significant trauma to occupants.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Stopped SUV on 8 Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734294/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734294/</guid><description>A northbound SUV struck the rear of a stopped SUV on 8 Avenue in Manhattan. The striking driver suffered a head injury and whiplash. Police cite driver inattention and following too closely as contributing factors in the collision.</description></item><item><title>SUV Rear-Ends Taxi in Manhattan Traffic</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804094/</guid><description>An SUV struck a stopped taxi on East 120th Street, injuring a passenger with neck trauma. The crash unfolded in slow-moving traffic, with driver distraction cited. The impact left the taxi damaged and a passenger suffering whiplash.</description></item><item><title>SUV Right Turn Hits 12-Year-Old Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734731/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4734731/</guid><description>A 12-year-old boy riding east on West 145 Street was struck by a westbound SUV making a right turn. The collision caused head injuries and bruising. Police cite the SUV driver’s disregard for traffic control and inexperience as key factors.</description></item><item><title>SUV Right Turn Strikes Bicyclist on West 145 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4733641/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4733641/</guid><description>A 33-year-old bicyclist suffered facial injuries and unconsciousness after an SUV making a right turn hit him on West 145 Street in Manhattan. The collision caused minor bleeding and left side damage to the SUV. Driver inattention was a key factor.</description></item><item><title>SUV Right-Turn Hits Bicyclist on Lenox Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4708724/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4708724/</guid><description>A 30-year-old male bicyclist suffered knee and lower leg injuries after a southbound SUV made a right turn and struck him on Lenox Avenue. The bike showed no damage. Police cite bicyclist confusion as a contributing factor to the crash.</description></item><item><title>SUV Slams Bike on Saint Nicholas Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4761533/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4761533/</guid><description>An SUV struck a bike near West 141st. Two men thrown. Legs torn, blood on blacktop. The bike twisted, SUV front crushed. Both riders conscious. One was a child. Alcohol played its part. The city’s danger revealed in steel and flesh.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes 12-Year-Old Pedestrian at Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4715390/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4715390/</guid><description>A 12-year-old girl suffered knee and lower leg abrasions after an SUV failed to yield while making a left turn. The driver’s inattention caused the collision at West 125 Street in Manhattan, leaving the pedestrian in shock.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Bicyclist on E 132 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4782591/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4782591/</guid><description>A 59-year-old male bicyclist was ejected and suffered head injuries after an SUV struck him on E 132 St in Manhattan. The collision occurred as both traveled eastbound. Police cite the SUV driver’s failure to yield right-of-way as the cause.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Bicyclist on Lenox Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4720993/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4720993/</guid><description>A northbound SUV collided with a westbound bicyclist on Lenox Avenue. The cyclist suffered knee and lower leg injuries, sustaining contusions and shock. Police cite driver inattention and distraction as key factors in the crash.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Bicyclist on St. Nicholas Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4802075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4802075/</guid><description>A 32-year-old male bicyclist suffered chest injuries and shock after a collision with a northbound SUV on St. Nicholas Avenue. The SUV was parked before impact. Police cite improper lane usage and driver distraction as causes. No vehicle damage reported.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Cyclist on Lenox Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4809800/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4809800/</guid><description>An SUV hit a cyclist on Lenox Avenue near West 118th. The cyclist suffered back injuries and shock. Police cite driver inattention and failure to yield. The crash left pain and confusion in its wake. The street stayed dangerous.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Pedestrian at Bradhurst Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804900/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804900/</guid><description>A woman crossing at W 142nd Street and Bradhurst Avenue was hit by a northbound SUV. She suffered abrasions and a shoulder injury, standing in shock as emergency crews arrived. The air was tense, sirens echoing off nearby buildings.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Pedestrian at Manhattan Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4750290/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4750290/</guid><description>A 32-year-old woman suffered knee and lower leg injuries after an SUV hit her on West 111 Street. The driver, distracted and inexperienced, struck the pedestrian at the intersection, causing contusions and bruises. The victim remained conscious after impact.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Pedestrian Crossing Against Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4756163/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4756163/</guid><description>A 53-year-old man was injured crossing East 131 Street in Manhattan. The SUV hit him on the right front quarter panel, causing back injuries. The pedestrian was incoherent at the scene. The driver was traveling straight southbound at impact.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Pedestrian Crossing with Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4752342/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4752342/</guid><description>A 50-year-old woman suffered arm injuries and shock after an SUV struck her at a Manhattan intersection. The driver failed to yield right-of-way, hitting the pedestrian as she crossed legally. The impact caused center front-end damage to the vehicle.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Pedestrian Crossing With Signal</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4793497/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4793497/</guid><description>A 68-year-old woman suffered head injuries and shock after an SUV struck her at an intersection on West 125th Street. The driver was making a left turn and distracted, hitting the pedestrian crossing with the signal. Abrasions marked the impact.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Pedestrian in Harlem Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804750/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4804750/</guid><description>A Cadillac SUV turning right on West 124th Street struck a 69-year-old woman crossing with the signal. She remained conscious, suffering a contusion to her lower leg. The crash left the pedestrian bruised and shaken on the pavement.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Pedestrian Playing in Manhattan Roadway</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4770588/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4770588/</guid><description>An SUV traveling east on W 125 St hit a male pedestrian playing in the roadway at an intersection. The pedestrian was injured and incoherent after impact. The vehicle sustained damage to its left front bumper. Driver errors remain unspecified.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Pedestrian Playing on Harlem River Drive</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4799765/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4799765/</guid><description>A 28-year-old man playing in the roadway on Harlem River Drive was struck by an SUV traveling south. The impact to the vehicle’s left front bumper caused knee and lower leg injuries, leaving the pedestrian in shock with internal complaints.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Sedan Turning Right Injuring Child Passenger</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731443/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731443/</guid><description>An SUV traveling north collided with a sedan making a right turn on West 145 Street in Manhattan. The impact struck the sedan’s right rear bumper. An 11-year-old front-seat passenger suffered head injuries and whiplash, enduring shock but was not ejected.</description></item><item><title>SUV Strikes Teen Bicyclist on West 135 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724625/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724625/</guid><description>A 16-year-old girl riding east on West 135 Street was injured when an SUV traveling north hit her on the bike&amp;rsquo;s left side. The impact caused bruising and lower leg injuries. The driver failed to yield right-of-way, compounding the crash.</description></item><item><title>SUV Swings Wide, Strikes Cyclist’s Leg on 8th Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4708035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4708035/</guid><description>A Toyota swung wide in a U-turn. Its bumper caught a cyclist’s leg. Flesh tore, blood pooled. The man stayed conscious as the SUV kept moving. The street bore witness to driver error and the cost paid in flesh.</description></item><item><title>SUV Turning Left Slams Cyclist on 8th Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4743142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4743142/</guid><description>An SUV turning left on 8th Avenue struck a northbound cyclist. The man flew, hit pavement, head split, blood pooled. Shock froze his eyes. The SUV’s bumper bent where his body broke. Night swallowed the scene in Manhattan.</description></item><item><title>SUV Turns Left, Strikes Pedestrian Head-On</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4805283/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4805283/</guid><description>At Lenox Avenue and West 142nd Street, a Nissan SUV’s bumper hit a woman’s head as she crossed with the signal. She stayed conscious, blood rising under her skin. The driver remained in his seat. The street pulsed with sirens.</description></item><item><title>SUV U-Turn Hits Eastbound Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4779927/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4779927/</guid><description>A BMW SUV making a U-turn struck a 39-year-old male bicyclist traveling east on W 116 St. The cyclist suffered knee and lower leg injuries and was in shock. Police cited driver inattention as a key factor in the collision.</description></item><item><title>SUVs Collide on East 119th Street, Injuring Driver</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4736274/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4736274/</guid><description>Two SUVs crashed on East 119th Street in Manhattan. The female driver of the southbound Tesla SUV suffered head injuries and whiplash. Police cite a malfunctioning traffic control device as a contributing factor. The impact struck the Tesla’s right side doors.</description></item><item><title>SUVs Collide on Lenox Avenue, Driver Injured</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4699212/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4699212/</guid><description>Two SUVs collided at Lenox Avenue and West 131 Street in Manhattan. The female driver of a southbound Hyundai SUV suffered knee and lower leg injuries. Police cited failure to yield right-of-way as the contributing factor in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Taxi and E-Bike Collide on 7 Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4728663/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4728663/</guid><description>A taxi and an e-bike collided head-on on 7 Avenue. The e-bike driver, a 28-year-old man, suffered a fractured shoulder and dislocation. Police cited driver inattention and distraction as key factors in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Taxi and Sedan Collide on East 125 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4703308/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4703308/</guid><description>A taxi and a sedan collided at East 125 Street and Lexington Avenue in Manhattan. The sedan driver, a 34-year-old woman, suffered back injuries and whiplash. Both vehicles sustained front-end damage. The crash highlights risks from driver errors in busy intersections.</description></item><item><title>Taxi and Sedan Collide on W 133 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4783132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4783132/</guid><description>A taxi traveling south struck a sedan making a U-turn on W 133 St in Manhattan. The impact injured a 27-year-old female passenger in the sedan, causing head trauma and whiplash. Driver distraction by electronic device contributed to the crash.</description></item><item><title>Taxi and Sedan Collide on West 127 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4714830/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4714830/</guid><description>A distracted driver caused a collision involving a taxi and two sedans on West 127 Street in Manhattan. Three men suffered back injuries and shock, all restrained or seated inside vehicles. The crash exposed dangers of driver inattention in busy city streets.</description></item><item><title>Taxi and SUV Collide on Slippery St Nicholas Ave</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4784759/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4784759/</guid><description>A taxi and an SUV collided on St Nicholas Ave in Manhattan. The taxi driver, impaired by alcohol, struck the SUV’s left side. The SUV driver was injured and incoherent. Slippery pavement contributed to the crash’s severity and impact.</description></item><item><title>Taxi and Van Collision Injures Four Passengers</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4759384/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4759384/</guid><description>A taxi and a van collided on 8 Avenue in Manhattan, injuring four male passengers. The crash involved driver inattention and limited visibility. Injuries included back, knee, and arm trauma. All occupants remained conscious and were not ejected from their vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Door Strikes E-Bike Rider in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4721209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4721209/</guid><description>A southbound e-bike rider was injured after colliding with a taxi&amp;rsquo;s left side doors. The rider was ejected and suffered abrasions to the arm. Passenger distraction in the taxi contributed to the crash, highlighting driver inattention in a busy Manhattan corridor.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Driver Distracted, Injures Two Passengers</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4735131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4735131/</guid><description>A taxi traveling north on Harlem River Drive struck another vehicle, injuring its driver and a teenage passenger. Both suffered contusions and bruises. The crash was caused by driver inattention and distraction, leading to a front-end collision.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Hits Cyclist on Left Side in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4755223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4755223/</guid><description>A taxi struck a cyclist on his left side at West 133rd and Lenox Avenue. The rider crashed hard, blood pooling at his waist. Four passengers watched silently. The bike lay twisted. The cyclist suffered severe abdominal injuries.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Hits Pedestrian at Manhattan Intersection</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4703904/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4703904/</guid><description>A 66-year-old man was injured crossing West 120 Street in Manhattan when a taxi struck him at the right rear quarter panel. The pedestrian suffered abrasions and lower leg injuries. The crash stemmed from driver inattention and passing too closely.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Hits Pedestrian Crossing St Nicholas Ave</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4782466/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4782466/</guid><description>A 25-year-old woman was struck while crossing St Nicholas Ave at a marked crosswalk. The taxi driver, distracted and inattentive, hit her with the vehicle’s front center. She suffered upper leg and hip injuries, left in shock at the scene.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Hits Pedestrian on W 125 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4773196/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4773196/</guid><description>A taxi traveling east on W 125 St struck a 35-year-old male pedestrian crossing without a signal. The pedestrian suffered bruises over his entire body. The driver’s inattention caused the collision, highlighting dangers of distracted driving in Manhattan.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Left Turn Collides With Sedan Going Straight</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4707742/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4707742/</guid><description>A taxi making a left turn struck a sedan traveling straight on 5 Avenue in Manhattan. Both drivers suffered chest injuries and shock. The impact damaged the front ends of both vehicles. Driver errors remain unspecified in the police report.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Left Turn Strikes Westbound Bicyclist</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731777/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731777/</guid><description>A taxi making a left turn collided with a westbound bicyclist on West 115 Street. The cyclist suffered knee and lower leg injuries with minor bleeding. Police cite driver inattention as the cause. The cyclist was not ejected and was in shock.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Passes Too Closely, Injures Pedestrian</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4738595/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4738595/</guid><description>A 64-year-old woman crossing with the signal was struck by a taxi passing too closely at a Manhattan intersection. The impact caused a back injury, leaving her conscious but seriously hurt. The driver made no evasive maneuvers, and the vehicle showed no damage.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Rear-Ends Sedan on St Nicholas Ave</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4772843/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4772843/</guid><description>A taxi driver fell asleep and rear-ended a stopped sedan on St Nicholas Ave in Manhattan. Three men in the sedan suffered back injuries and whiplash. The crash caused left rear bumper damage to the sedan and front-end damage to the taxi.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Slams Cyclist, Head Trauma on 111th Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4732710/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4732710/</guid><description>A taxi struck a 67-year-old cyclist at West 111th and 8th Avenue. The rider flew from his bike, head split, blood pooling on the street. Evening fell as he lay incoherent, victim of driver distraction and failure to yield.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Strikes Bicyclist on W 131 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4787643/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4787643/</guid><description>A taxi parked on Frederick Douglass Blvd struck a southbound bicyclist on W 131 St. The cyclist was ejected, suffering back injuries and shock. Police cite improper lane usage by the taxi as the cause of the collision.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Strikes Bicyclist Turning Improperly in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4778168/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4778168/</guid><description>A 65-year-old male bicyclist was injured and ejected after a taxi struck him during a right turn on W 152 St. The crash caused chest injuries and shock. Police cite the taxi driver’s failure to yield and the cyclist’s improper turning as factors.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Strikes Pedestrian Crossing Outside Crosswalk</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4801591/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4801591/</guid><description>A 24-year-old woman was injured crossing West 145th Street outside a crosswalk. A taxi making a left turn struck her with its left front bumper. Limited driver visibility contributed to the collision, causing upper leg injuries to the pedestrian.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Strikes Pedestrian on West 137 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4767187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4767187/</guid><description>A taxi traveling east on West 137 Street struck a 28-year-old female pedestrian outside an intersection. The pedestrian suffered an upper arm contusion. The crash involved driver inattention and unsafe speed, with impact on the taxi’s right front quarter panel.</description></item><item><title>Taxi Strikes Rear Passenger on E 135 St</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4780136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4780136/</guid><description>A taxi, parked westbound on E 135 St, struck a rear passenger inside the vehicle. The 23-year-old female occupant suffered neck abrasions. The impact damaged the taxi’s left rear quarter panel. No driver errors were cited in the police report.</description></item><item><title>Toyota Strikes Elderly Man on W 135th Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4769074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4769074/</guid><description>A 66-year-old man lay dying on W 135th Street, crushed by a westbound Toyota. His head shattered, organs ruptured. The streetlights glared down as life left his body. The car rolled on, the city’s danger exposed again.</description></item><item><title>Truck-Sedan Collision Injures Child Passenger</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4737251/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4737251/</guid><description>A tractor truck and sedan collided on East 125 Street in Manhattan. A 9-year-old passenger suffered back contusions. Limited view contributed to the crash. The sedan was changing lanes when struck by the truck going straight. No ejections occurred.</description></item><item><title>Turning Sedan Crushes Pedestrian at Harlem Corner</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4701162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4701162/</guid><description>A sedan swung right on West 144th. Its bumper struck a man crossing with the signal. Bones broke. He stayed conscious. The street bore the wound. The driver failed to yield. The city’s danger showed its teeth.</description></item><item><title>Turning SUV Fatally Strikes Toddler Pedestrian</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4739974/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4739974/</guid><description>A three-year-old girl crossing with the signal on Lenox Avenue was struck in the head by a turning SUV. She died at the scene. The SUV’s front end bore the impact, marking the fatal collision.</description></item><item><title>Two Passengers Injured as Drivers Ignore Signals</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4806800/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4806800/</guid><description>Metal screeched on W 135 St at Edgecombe Ave. Two women in the back seat felt the jolt—pain in the arm, nausea, shock. Sirens echoed as traffic stopped. Both sedans bore fresh scars, their front ends crumpled in the late-day light.</description></item><item><title>Two Sedans Collide on E 125 St in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4777291/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4777291/</guid><description>Two sedans traveling southbound on E 125 St collided head-to-back late at night. Both drivers suffered moderate injuries including neck and back abrasions. The crash caused center front and back end damage to the vehicles, with no ejections reported.</description></item><item><title>Two Sedans Collide on E 130 St, Passenger Injured</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4802472/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4802472/</guid><description>A left-turning sedan struck another sedan traveling straight on E 130 St in Manhattan. The impact injured a 19-year-old rear-seat passenger, who suffered shoulder and upper arm injuries. Both drivers were licensed women. Damage concentrated on front bumpers and quarter panel.</description></item><item><title>Two Sedans Collide on East 112 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4712305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4712305/</guid><description>Two sedans traveling north on East 112 Street collided, injuring passengers in both vehicles. The crash involved unsafe lane changing and passing too closely. Both injured occupants suffered neck injuries and shock, highlighting driver errors as the cause.</description></item><item><title>Two Sedans Collide on Edgecombe Avenue</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4731211/</guid><description>Two sedans collided on Edgecombe Avenue in Manhattan. The 62-year-old male driver suffered a hip and upper leg injury and was in shock. The crash involved multiple vehicles and was caused by vehicular errors, according to the police report.</description></item><item><title>Two Sedans Collide on Harlem River Drive</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4760664/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4760664/</guid><description>Two sedans collided on Harlem River Drive at 6:30 a.m. Both drivers and a passenger suffered injuries ranging from whiplash to upper arm trauma. The crash involved defective accelerator and other vehicular factors, causing shock and bodily harm.</description></item><item><title>Two SUVs Collide on West 145 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4733642/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4733642/</guid><description>Two sport utility vehicles collided on West 145 Street in Manhattan. The impact struck the left rear bumper of one SUV and the left front bumper of the other. A 56-year-old female driver suffered neck injuries and whiplash, according to the police report.</description></item><item><title>Unlicensed Bicyclist Ejected in Manhattan Taxi Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4743025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4743025/</guid><description>A 60-year-old male bicyclist was ejected and injured in a collision with a taxi on West 131 Street. Both vehicles struck front center. The bicyclist suffered neck contusions and bruises. The bicyclist was unlicensed, and the taxi driver was licensed.</description></item><item><title>Unlicensed Driver Crashes Sedan into SUV in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4766157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4766157/</guid><description>A sedan driven by an unlicensed man struck the rear of a southbound SUV on East 132 Street. The SUV driver suffered hip and upper leg injuries and was incoherent at the scene. Alcohol involvement was noted in the crash report.</description></item><item><title>Unlicensed Driver Rear-Ends Taxi in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724356/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4724356/</guid><description>A 40-year-old unlicensed sedan driver struck a stopped taxi on West 125th Street. The impact caused neck injuries and whiplash. Police cite driver inattention and following too closely as key factors in the crash.</description></item><item><title>Unlicensed Moped Driver Ejects Child Passenger</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4808218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4808218/</guid><description>A moped and sedan collided on Frederick Douglass Blvd at W 155 St. An 11-year-old girl riding as a rear passenger on the moped was ejected and injured, suffering abrasions to her lower leg. Sirens echoed as first responders arrived.</description></item><item><title>Unlicensed Motorcyclist Crashes Into SUV on Harlem River Drive</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4732517/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4732517/</guid><description>A motorcycle driver, unlicensed and changing lanes unsafely, collided with a Jeep SUV traveling north on Harlem River Drive. The motorcyclist, following too closely, struck the SUV’s right front bumper, sustaining abrasions to his elbow and lower arm.</description></item><item><title>Unlicensed Scooter Driver Ejected in Manhattan Crash</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4727867/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4727867/</guid><description>A motorscooter driver was ejected and injured in a collision with a sedan on Madison Avenue. The scooter driver, unlicensed, suffered shoulder and upper arm abrasions. The sedan, driven by a licensed female, struck the scooter from behind while both traveled northbound.</description></item><item><title>Unlicensed Sedan Rear-Ends Taxi on Harlem River Drive</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4796786/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4796786/</guid><description>A 27-year-old licensed taxi driver suffered neck injuries after a collision on Harlem River Drive. The unlicensed sedan driver struck the taxi’s left rear bumper while both vehicles traveled northbound. The crash caused whiplash and center-end damage to both vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Van Strikes Bicyclist on West 145 Street</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4722311/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4722311/</guid><description>A van and a bicycle collided head-on on West 145 Street. The 18-year-old bicyclist was partially ejected and suffered facial contusions. According to the police report, both vehicles were traveling eastbound when the impact occurred at the bike’s front center and van’s left front quarter panel.</description></item><item><title>Westbound Car Strikes Pedestrian Head-On in Harlem</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4722288/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4722288/</guid><description>A westbound car hit a 60-year-old man head-on on East 119th Street. His head split open. Blood ran. He stayed conscious. The street kept moving. The crash left him bleeding, the city indifferent, the danger unyielding.</description></item><item><title>White Van Strikes Parked Sedan in Manhattan</title><link>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4753109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://crashcountnyc.com/events/9/4753109/</guid><description>A white van making a left turn collided with a parked sedan on West 152 Street in Manhattan. The impact damaged the right rear quarter panels of both vehicles. The sedan’s occupant, a 53-year-old man, suffered back injuries and shock.</description></item></channel></rss>